so really quickly my name is cornelio
很快我的名字叫Cornelio
Davis I am the director of platform
戴维斯（Davis）我是平台主管
engineering for cloud foundry so I'm at
云铸造的工程，所以我在
pivotal I have been working with I just
我一直在与我合作
realized it's September already I've
意识到我已经是九月了
been working with cloud foundry for
一直在与Cloud Foundry合作
about three years I came to pivotal from
大约三年后，我从
EMC where I worked in the corporate CTO
我在公司CTO工作的EMC
office and we did emerging tech there
办公室，我们在那里做新兴技术
and about three years ago I was rolling
大约三年前，
off of a project in my boss Tom Maguire
我老板汤姆·马奎尔（Tom Maguire）的一个项目
at the time said hey you know I want you
当时说嘿，你知道我想要你
to start looking at this new thing
开始看这个新东西
called pass relatively new and so I
叫做通行证相对较新，所以我
started looking into that and of course
开始调查，当然
we were EMC and cloud foundry was VMware
我们是EMC，云代工厂是VMware
so I started looking at cloud foundry
所以我开始研究云代工厂
then and about a year ago I joined cloud
然后大约一年前，我加入了云
I joined the cloud foundry team proper
我正确地加入了Cloud Foundry团队
from this platform engineering role
从这个平台工程角色
platform engineering is a very small
平台工程很小
engineering group we're in the product
产品中的工程团队
team but we're field facing so I spend
团队，但我们面对现场，所以我花了
virtually all of my time working with
我几乎所有的时间都在与
large strategic customers as well as
大型战略客户以及
partners kind of pushing the envelope
合作伙伴有点推波助澜
with cloud foundry
与云铸造
so definitely hands-on technical and so
所以绝对动手技术等等
you'll you'll hear a lot of the kind of
你会听到很多这样的
reflections throughout the talk on that
整个演讲过程中的思考
and so and introducing also my colleague
因此，还介绍了我的同事
Josh Kruk who works with me at pivotal
Josh Kruk和我一起工作于枢纽
go ahead I'm Josh Kruk I I work on the
继续吧，我是Josh Kruk II，
sister team to Cornelia's in the
姐妹队去科妮莉亚的
customer success office
客户成功办公室
my role is 50% customer facing helping
我的角色是50％的客户需要帮助
people be successful with cloud foundry
人们通过Cloud Foundry获得成功
so that's deployment and operations and
这就是部署和操作，
also a lot of app development how do you
还有很多应用程序开发你如何
transition your apps or how do you write
转换您的应用程序或如何编写
new apps to take advantage of kind of
新应用可以利用
the third platform and then the other
第三个平台，然后另一个
half of my time is also spent focused in
我一半的时间也花在了
product my passions kind of utilities
产品我的激情那种实用程序
and tooling around cloud foundry and
和围绕云铸造的工具
making apps that work on the platform or
制作可在平台上运行的应用程序或
against the platform itself for
针对平台本身
operations awesome thank you all right
很棒的行动谢谢你
so what we want to talk about this
所以我们想谈谈这个
morning is you've already heard tons and
早上你已经听到很多声音了
tons of the phrase cloud native and
数以千计的短语cloud native和
you've probably also heard people talk
您可能还听过人们的谈话
about 12 factor apps and the short of it
大约12个因素的应用程序及其不足之处
is that the way that we used to build
就是我们过去的建造方式
application
应用
in the last couple of decades is was
在过去的几十年中，
really optimized for the architectures
真正针对架构进行了优化
that we had back then and now the
那时候我们曾经有过
architectures fundamentally are
架构从根本上说是
different so to give you a little bit of
不一样，所以给你一点
a perspective I've been doing this for a
我一直在为此做一个观点
long time I'm going to date myself here
很长一段时间我要在这里约会
but I've been writing software for 25
但是我已经写了25年的软件
years and when I first started I started
多年，当我第一次开始时
in embedded systems and I compiled I
在嵌入式系统中，我编译了
wrote code and C or even a DES I was
写了代码，我什至是C甚至是DES
over I was in the defense industry and
我当时在国防行业
the most sophisticated thing that we did
我们所做的最复杂的事情
was we maybe we cross compiled so I
是我们也许我们交叉编译了，所以我
compiled on one machine and took the
在一台机器上编译并接受
binaries and ran them on another machine
二进制文件并在另一台计算机上运行它们
so there was nothing that was inherently
所以没有内在的东西
distributed and I also remember being
分散，我也记得
and we actually had one project where we
实际上我们有一个项目
had three processors and we actually had
有三个处理器，我们实际上有
a whiteboard that we drew out what was
我们画出了什么的白板
happening on the different processors
发生在不同的处理器上
and how we timed out how long things
以及我们如何超时多长时间
were going to take and where the
打算去哪里
handoffs were going to be it was very
交接将是非常
static and it was very very rigid and
静态的，它非常非常僵硬，
now everything's distributed right so
现在一切都散布了，所以
these these cell phones that we have
这些我们拥有的手机
didn't even exist the cloud didn't exist
甚至不存在云不存在
and so the way that we built
所以我们建立的方式
applications in the past was for the
过去的申请是为了
architectures that we had and the
我们拥有的架构以及
architectures have fundamentally changed
架构发生了根本变化
to be cloud now we'll talk about what
成为云现在我们将讨论什么
exactly does that mean in just a moment
确切地说这意味着
but because the underlying architectures
但是因为基础架构
have changed everything is distributed
改变了一切分配
now everything is always changing that
现在一切都在改变
old diagram with very rigid timings and
具有非常严格的计时的旧图和
so on that would just never fly in this
所以在那永远不会飞
world that fundamentally means that in
从根本上意味着
order to take advantage of that
为了利用这一点
architecture we need to change the way
建筑，我们需要改变方式
that we build our applications so you've
我们构建应用程序，以便您
heard about this thing called 12 factor
听说这件事叫做12因素
perhaps but what we want to do is really
也许，但是我们想要做的是
kind of demystify that a little bit in
有点神秘化
this talk get very concrete and say what
这个演讲很具体，说什么
are those 12 factors let's look at them
是这12个因素让我们来看一下
let's understand them a little bit think
让我们了解一下他们的想法
a little bit more deeply about them and
关于他们更深入一点
by the way even in an hour and a half
顺便说一个半小时
talk we can't think about them as we
谈论我们无法想像他们
can't talk about them and think about
不能谈论他们并思考
them as
他们作为
deeply as we should so hopefully what
深深地希望，我们应该如此
I'd like you all to take away from this
我希望大家都摆脱这个
is I really need to study these things I
我真的需要研究这些东西吗
need to I have an introduction now I
我现在需要介绍
need to study these various factors and
需要研究这些各种因素，并且
understand what they are and importantly
了解它们是什么，重要的是
why they're important because that's
为什么它们很重要，因为那是
going to be what enables you to build
将使您能够建立
your applications the right way and
您的应用程序是正确的方式
honestly be able to articulate it to
说实话能够表达
your colleagues who are not here at
您不在这里的同事
spring one so that's really our goal is
春天之一，所以这真的是我们的目标是
to get you understanding those things
让你了解那些事情
and thinking more deeply about them so
然后更深入地思考他们
what the heck is a cloud native
什么是云原生
application so there's whole bunches of
应用程序，所以有很多
definitions and attributes that people
人们的定义和属性
associate with cloud native applications
与云原生应用程序关联
and everybody's got a different
每个人都有不同
definition so I've pulled a couple of
定义，所以我拉了几个
them off here so that one of them that I
他们离开这里，所以我其中一个
found it was actually quote which is why
发现它实际上是报价，这就是为什么
it's in quotes has developed
用引号引起来的
specifically for cloud platforms and I'm
专为云平台而设计
like okay so what's a cloud platform
像这样，那么云平台是什么
that's like looking something up in the
这就像在
dictionary and they say you know I don't
字典，他们说你知道我不知道
know I should have had a better example
知道我应该有一个更好的例子
off the tip of my tongue but you know
离开我的舌尖，但你知道
you go to look up a word and it says oh
你去查一个字，它说哦
that's in the business of and they give
这是在做生意，他们给
you this shortened version of that word
你这个单词的缩写
so I doesn't tell me anything so what is
所以我什么也没告诉我
a cloud platform is it AWS is it Cloud
云平台是AWS还是云
Foundry not sure it's highly scalable
铸造厂不确定其高度可扩展性
absolutely no question and high
绝对没问题，很高
scalability really almost what I'm
可扩展性几乎就是我所需要的
thinking there's as soon as you have
想尽快有
more than one machine that's already
超过一台已经存在的机器
scalable you already have to deal with
您已经必须应对的可扩展性
some level of distribution and in many
某种程度的分布
cases it's very highly scalable so that
情况下，它具有很高的可扩展性，因此
seems about right
似乎是正确的
mobile yeah not always but probably a
是的，移动电话不一定，但可能
good idea and we'll talk a little bit
好主意，我们再谈一点
about if you got multiple devices that
关于您是否有多个设备
you're supporting what's one of the
您正在支持其中之一
factors that you might think about
您可能会考虑的因素
they're a jille definitely definitely in
他们绝对是吉尔
this world we are constantly releasing
这个世界，我们不断释放
software we need to have agility
我们需要敏捷的软件
not only agility in the software that
不仅软件的敏捷性
we're releasing but we need to have
我们要发布，但我们需要
agility because the platform that I'm
敏捷，因为我在平台上
running on is always always changing and
持续运行总是在变化，
we'll talk about that later in the talk
我们将在后面的讨论中
in more detail applications that run in
更详细地运行在
containers well actually I think that's
容器其实我认为那是
an implementation detail it really
真正的实现细节
doesn't matter we have things that are
没关系，我们拥有的是
out there running whether they run in
不管他们跑进去
containers or not really I don't think
容器与否我真的不认为
that that's part of the definition of
那是定义的一部分
cloud native applications micro-services
云本机应用程序微服务
Josh was teasing me this morning we
今天早上我们约瑟开玩笑
almost made it through the entire talk
在整个谈话中几乎都做到了
without putting the word microservices
不使用微服务这个词
on the slide but I snuck it in late last
在幻灯片上，但我在最后很晚才偷了它
night so here it is micro services
晚上，所以这里是微服务
probably and again we could go off and
大概一次又一次，我们可以出发
do a definition around micro services
对微服务进行定义
designed for failure without question
专为失败而设计
that's what I was just talking about
那就是我刚才所说的
things are always changing and we'll
事情总是在变化，我们会
talk a little bit more about design for
多谈一些设计
for failure so the other part of the
对于失败，所以另一部分
title so I've been talking about cloud
标题，所以我一直在谈论云
native in the first slide but if you
在第一张幻灯片中是本机的，但如果您
remember that the title of the talk had
请记住，演讲的标题
12 factor in it as well so 12 factor net
还有12因子，所以12因子净
if you haven't looked at it there's the
如果您没有看过的话
URL definitely worth a read it's pretty
网址绝对值得一读，很漂亮
short actually it's quite short and it
短，实际上很短，而且
talks about it was it was written by a
谈论它是由一个人写的
number of developers that worked at
工作过的开发人员数量
Heroku so Heroku was a platform as a
Heroku，因此Heroku是一个平台
service out there and people have been
服务在那里，人们一直在
deploying apps onto it and they kind of
在上面部署应用程序，它们有点
figured out what some of these patterns
找出其中的一些模式
were some of these factors work and so
这些因素中有些起作用吗？
we're starting with the 12 factor but
我们从12个因素开始
you'll see that we're actually going to
您会看到我们实际上将
go a little bit beyond that as well so
还要超出一点
12 factor is just a really great kind of
12个因素真是很棒
concise description of what some of
简要说明一些
these factors are so we're going to use
这些因素是我们将要使用的
that as kind of our guide this is um not
作为我们的指导，这不是
big on agenda slides but you can really
议程幻灯片上有很多内容，但您确实可以
think of 12 factor net is kind of the
想到12因子网就是那种
agenda that we're going to go through
我们要通过的议程
now the first factor then is code base
现在第一个因素是代码库
and you can see the subtitle there says
你会看到那里的字幕说
one code base tracked and revision
跟踪和修订一个代码库
control many deploys so obviously we
控制很多部署，所以很明显我们
need revision control so we're not going
需要版本控制，所以我们不会
to focus on that part of it that's just
专注于那一部分
table stakes but there's a bigger
赌桌赌注，但更大
question and by the way we're going to
问题，顺便说一句
work
工作
spend a lot of time not only going
花很多时间不仅要去
through slides actually that'll be the
通过幻灯片实际上这将是
smaller portion we're going to spend a
一小部分，我们将花费
lot of time inside of github and inside
在github内部和内部的大量时间
of the code and we're going to lose lots
代码，我们将损失很多
and lots of demos if the demo gods will
还有很多演示，如果演示之神会
have it so if you read the first factor
有它，所以如果您阅读第一个因素
it really is talking more about like I
真的像我一样在谈论更多
said repose or table stakes but how are
说的休息或桌子赌注，但如何
you breaking up your codebase that's
你打破你的代码库
really the fundamental questions
真正的根本问题
question there and they make the
问题在那里，他们使
assertion that one code base equals one
断言一个代码库等于一个
app now that seems relatively
应用程序现在似乎相对
straightforward although you can imagine
直截了当，虽然你可以想象
now that we'll wait a minute what if I
现在我们等一下，如果我
have a large complex system and it's
有一个大型的复杂系统，
really a composite application you could
真正的复合应用程序，您可以
say okay I've got a composite
说好吧，我有一个综合
application and that's made up of a
应用程序，它由一个
whole bunch of apps and we're going to
一堆应用程序，我们将
do a one-for-one mapping on that but
对此进行一对一映射，但是
really that's what this first factor is
真的，这就是第一个因素
challenging that first factor is getting
挑战首要因素
you to think about how do you break up
你想想你怎么分手
your code into different repositories
您的代码到不同的存储库
and the interesting thing is that
有趣的是
there's actually an organizational
实际上有一个组织
design question in there as well this is
那里的设计问题也是
that it seems like a super
好像超级好
straightforward but you can spend a lot
简单明了，但您可以花很多钱
of time just thinking about this so
只是在想这个
really the question is this mapping of
真正的问题是这种映射
one code base to one app is that really
一个应用程序的一个代码库就是
the way it goes and the answer is maybe
前进的方式，答案也许是
and let me take a moment here and say
让我在这里花点时间说
something that I wanted to emphasize
我想强调的东西
early on so these 12 factors are not not
尽早，所以这12个因素并不是
hard and fast rules it is not that you
严格的规则不是你
can't that you unless you follow all 12
不能，除非您全部遵循12
12 of them to the letter and by the way
他们中的12人来信并顺便说一句
it's so short that there's room for lots
太短了，有很多空间
of interpretation in there there is you
解释在那里
don't have to follow all 12 to the
不必跟随所有12到
letter hundred percent before you have a
信百分之一百之前，你有一个
cloud native application so you should
云本机应用程序，因此您应该
take a look at each one of these and
看看其中的每一个
really like I said think deeply about it
就像我说的那样深思熟虑
and think about what it means in terms
考虑一下它的含义
of your particular deployments so again
您的特定部署再次
the question the question is here and
问题在这里，
the answer is maybe so let's look at
答案可能是，所以让我们来看一下
some alternatives so I'm going to kind
一些替代方案，所以我会好心
of do a bit of a proof here and say well
在这里做一点证明并说好
I want to prove
我想证明
one code base equals one app so let's
一个代码库等于一个应用程序，所以让我们
look at some other things and basically
看一些其他的东西，基本上
show conflict so let's take a look at a
显示冲突，让我们看一下
couple of these because really it comes
其中的几个，因为它真的来了
down to that that's probably a pretty
到那可能是一个漂亮的
good rule one code base equals one app
好的规则，一个代码库等于一个应用程序
so let's look at those alternatives so
所以让我们来看看那些替代方案
this is something that we have done in
这是我们所做的
the past is one code base equals a whole
过去是一个代码库等于一个整体
lot of apps now we did package things up
现在我们已经打包了很多应用
in monoliths so you could in fact and
在整体中，因此您实际上可以
you probably thought of it that middle
你可能想到了那个中间
thing there the application as a single
事情在那里作为一个单一的应用程序
application but the reality is that you
应用程序，但现实是您
should be breaking that monolith up and
应该打破那块巨石，
and I spend a lot of time with with very
我花了很多时间与
large clients who that's their biggest
那些最大的大客户
question is I've got these legacy
问题是我有这些遗产
monoliths and I know I'm having all this
巨石，我知道我拥有这一切
pain around it because it's hard to rev
痛苦，因为它很难修复
and it's hard to even get a team to be
而且甚至很难组建一个团队
able to grok what's in that monolith and
能够窥探那块巨石中的东西，
start being effective on building code
开始有效地构建代码
and so on so they know what they want to
等等，以便他们知道他们想要什么
break these things up so rather than
分解这些东西而不是
asking the question of what one code
问什么代码的问题
base equals many apps it's really one
基本等于许多应用程序，这实际上是一个
code base for for what should be many
什么应该有很多的代码库
apps now of course this here is an
现在的应用程序当然这是一个
anti-pattern we are working away from
反模式，我们正在远离
the monoliths the other thing that I'll
巨石我会做的另一件事
tell you in working with customers is we
告诉您与客户合作是我们
sometimes have customers that say ok I
有时候有些顾客说可以
want to try out Cloud Foundry and I want
想尝试Cloud Foundry，我想
to take an existing app and you know
拿一个现有的应用程序，你知道
what how about Documentum or how about
Documentum怎么样？
Liferay can I run that on your platform
Liferay我可以在您的平台上运行它吗
and the answer is no no no no cloud
答案是不，不，不，不，云
native doesn't mean you take the
本机并不意味着您会选择
existing all of the legacy baggage with
现有的所有旧行李
you over into the cloud cloud native
您进入云原生
means that you're getting rid of some of
意味着您要摆脱一些
that baggage so this is really an
那个行李，所以这真的是一个
anti-pattern but it's something that we
反模式，但这是我们
can migrate from and like I said a lot
可以像我所说的那样迁移
of customers are working from that so
的客户因此而工作
this one kind of let's put this one off
这一种让我们推迟
to the side when it comes to migration
在迁移方面
I'm just going to make a couple of
我只是要做几个
comments here we have a couple of talks
评论在这里，我们有几个讲座
that will reference at the end of the
在末尾引用
slides
滑梯
that and other talks here at spring one
一春季在这里进行的那场谈话
this one migrating the monolith
这一个迁移的整体
unfortunately already passed how many
不幸的是已经通过了多少
people made it to row heats talk
人们热闹非凡
yesterday a handful of you that's great
昨天你们当中有几个很棒
so reheat spoke yesterday afternoon on
所以昨天下午再热
migrating the monolith the good news is
迁移整体，好消息是
that all of these are being recorded so
所有这些都被记录下来
I would encourage you to go back and
我鼓励你回去
take a look at that one once the
看一下那个
recordings are made available but really
提供了录音，但实际上
when it comes to migration there's some
关于迁移，有一些
patterns that we can follow so there's
我们可以遵循的模式
some prerequisites you want to make sure
您需要确保的一些先决条件
you have adequate test coverage and
您有足够的测试范围，并且
pipelines in the same build environment
同一构建环境中的管道
then you want to choose things very
那你就很想选择东西
carefully what do I want to pull out of
仔细地我想从中取出什么
the monolith make sure that you can
整体确保您可以
demonstrate value in the extraction you
在提取中展示价值
extract the thing now here's the key
提取东西，现在这是关键
when you extract that component what
当您提取该组件时，
you're doing now is you're creating a
您现在正在做的是创建一个
separate app a separate app that's maybe
单独的应用程序
its own repository or that has to be its
它自己的存储库，或者必须是它的
own repository so now you're moving back
拥有自己的存储库，所以现在您要移回
toward that one for one mapping and then
朝那个一对一的映射，然后
you can do things like put proxy
你可以做代理之类的事情
patterns in place inside of the monolith
整体内部的图案
so that's just a really quick high
所以这是一个非常快的高
overview of the migrating the monolith
整体迁移的概述
and so on this first one we kind of get
等等，这是第一个
back to okay maybe it is that one for
回到好吧，也许是因为
one mapping there we go new repository
一个映射在那里，我们去了新的仓库
circling the emphasis that I made well
盘旋我做得很好的重点
what about a lot of code bases equaling
那么很多代码库等于
one application let's look at a scenario
一个应用程序让我们看一个场景
here this was actually one that was
这实际上是一个
brought up when we were talking about
在我们谈论时长大
this with a colleague of ours Josh
和我们乔希的同事一起
McEntee and he suggested that perhaps
McEntee和他建议也许
you might have a single code base that
您可能只有一个代码库
has two different processes running in
有两个不同的进程正在运行
it that are going to get deployed as two
它将被部署为两个
different apps so for example here
不同的应用程序，例如这里
you've got a web interface that is
您有一个Web界面
accessing something that's maybe in
访问可能在
queueing work so I'm scheduling a
排队工作，所以我要安排一个
doctor's appointment and now I want to
医生的任命，现在我想
queue up something that says before I
在我排队之前说些什么
get to that doctor's appointment please
请去看那个医生的约会
make sure that you've transferred all of
确保您已转移所有
my medical records from the cloud down
我的病历从云端降下来
to the doctor's office the local
到当地的医生办公室
doctor's office so the little grey box
医生的办公室，所以小灰盒
in the little green box those are the
在绿色的小盒子里是
two different apps
两个不同的应用
and could we say that that's a single
我们可以说那是一个
codebase that really is just one app but
实际上只是一个应用程序的代码库
two different processes so let's suspend
两个不同的过程，让我们暂停
disbelief for a moment and think about
难以置信片刻，想一想
that so maybe that's a decent scenario
所以也许这是一个不错的情况
so I've got these two different apps but
所以我有这两个不同的应用程序，但是
if you start to think about it if you've
如果你开始考虑的话
got um in fact I'm sorry he we were
嗯，其实我很抱歉他
talking about here about having two
在这里谈论有两个
different code bases two different
不同的代码库两个不同
repositories single app but if you've
存储库单个应用程序，但是如果您已经
got two different repositories you're
有两个不同的存储库
probably talking about two different
大概在谈论两个不同
teams or you're enabling two different
团队，或者您要启用两个不同的
teams to work on those two different
团队来从事这两个不同的工作
pizza box teams right and as soon as you
比萨盒团队就在您身边
have two teams
有两个团队
you probably want an API because in
您可能需要API，因为
order for two different teams to work on
命令两个不同的团队一起工作
things turns out that interfaces are a
事实证明，接口是一个
really great way of thinking about
非常好的思考方式
Organa organizing your development teams
Organa组织您的开发团队
so if you can separate if you can put an
因此，如果可以分开，可以放一个
API there then you can separate out your
API，然后您就可以分离出
development teams which means you can
开发团队，这意味着您可以
scale your development so that's two
扩展您的开发范围，以便两个
factor one code base so we come back to
分解一个代码库，所以我们回到
the question of one code base equals one
一个代码库的问题等于一个
app yep probably that's probably a good
是的，可能是个好习惯
idea so let's do a little bit of an
想法，让我们做一点
aside here we talked about the fact that
除了在这里，我们谈论的事实是
we were going to talk about twelve and
我们将要谈论十二点
now I will let you know that that's not
现在我会让你知道那不是
all we're actually going to talk about a
我们实际上将要谈论的是
number of other factors that we think
我们认为的其他因素数量
are important as well so here's one of
也很重要，所以这是其中之一
the first bonus factors by the way
顺便说一句第一奖金因素
you'll notice that we're not going to go
您会注意到我们不会去
through the factors in order so from 1
通过从1开始的因素
through 12 we're going to go through
到12点，我们将经历
them in an order that seems to make a
他们的顺序似乎使
bit more sense to us so here's a bonus
对我们来说更有意义，所以这是奖金
factor and that is when you're designing
因素，那就是在设计时
your applications think about API first
您的应用程序首先考虑API
think about the interfaces how your
考虑一下接口如何
micro services are there it is again
微服务又来了
micro services was there before I um
我之前有微服务
think about designing them even
考虑甚至设计它们
developing those api's first so one of
开发那些api的第一个，因此
the great things that you can do and one
您可以做的一件伟大的事
of the things that you can do to enable
您可以做的事情
testability
可测性
is to create implementations of your API
是创建您的API的实现
so that our mocks so in order to be able
这样我们的模拟游戏才能
to do testing in a highly distributed
在高度分散的环境中进行测试
environment you need to have mocks of
您需要模拟的环境
different different API s and different
不同的不同的API和不同的
services so even developing even before
服务，甚至在发展之前
you put the real implementation back
你把真正的实现放回去
there you can develop mocks for your ap
在那里您可以为您的AP开发模拟
is you need to version your API s you
您是否需要对API进行版本控制
need to be able to discover the api's
需要能够发现api的
and so on so there's a whole community
等等，整个社区
out there that's that's really involved
真正涉及到的是
in API development and API management
在API开发和API管理中
and you can see there there's a URL
你会看到那里有一个URL
that's API first comm so have a look
这是API的第一次交流，所以看看
there really really good information all
那里真的有非常好的信息
right
对
factor number two says dependencies
第二个因素说依赖性
explicitly declare and isolate
明确声明和隔离
dependencies so the first thing that I
依赖，所以我的第一件事
want to say is you need to ask the
想说的是你需要问
question of why because that's really
为什么这样的问题，因为那是真的
what's motivating it so why are we doing
是什么激励着我们，为什么要做
this well clearly we're all developers
很明显，我们都是开发人员
it's really to make our lives easier
确实是让我们的生活更轻松
right it's all about us and I a
对，这一切都与我们有关，我
career-long developer here so I include
在这里从事职业生涯的开发人员，所以我包括
myself in there so it's all about the
我自己在那里，这就是关于
developer avoiding dependency hell right
开发人员避免依赖地狱权
so and I know that spring 1 is a
所以我知道春天1是一个
developer conference I go to other
我去其他的开发者大会
conferences like DevOps days where it's
像DevOps这样的会议
completely skewed the other way where
完全歪斜，相反
it's a room full of operations folks and
这是一个充满操作人员的房间，
I realize that most of you are probably
我意识到你们大多数人可能是
developers but eventually your apps well
开发人员，但最终您的应用程序运行良好
hopefully if they see the light of day
希望如果他们看到了曙光
be operated by you in production so it's
由您在生产中操作，因此
not only about making our developers
不只是让我们的开发人员
lives easier but it's also about making
生活更轻松，但这也与
operations lives easier and what one of
操作更轻松，其中哪一项
the things that we absolutely have to
我们绝对必须要做的事情
have on the operations side is
在操作方面是
repeatable deployments if I cannot
如果我不能重复部署
repeatedly deploy or if I cannot deploy
反复部署或如果我无法部署
throughout the entire life application
在整个生命周期中的应用
life cycle without huge hurdles coming
没有巨大障碍的生命周期
up then that's really going to stymie my
那真的会阻碍我
ability to be very agile in this new
在新产品中变得非常敏捷的能力
world so let's take a little deep
世界，让我们深入一点
for a moment and talk about that in a
片刻，然后在
bit more depth so I'm going to jump over
多一点的深度，所以我要跳过
to factor five I'll come back to factor
分解为五，我将回到分解
two in just a moment so factor 5 says
一会儿就有两个，因数5说
strictly separate those those different
严格区分那些不同的人
stages in the application strictly
严格的申请阶段
separate factor factor five in 12 factor
十二因子中的五因子
actually talks about build release and
实际谈论的是版本发布和
run what we like to do is we like to add
运行我们想做的就是添加
the design phase as well now I want to
在设计阶段，现在我想
take just a moment here to talk about
花一点时间在这里谈论
those different phases and talk about
那些不同的阶段并谈论
who's up who's doing those what you're
谁来了谁在做那些你在做什么
doing and then why why don't we want to
然后为什么我们不想
merge that with some of the other phases
将其与其他一些阶段合并
why do we want to create this strict
我们为什么要创建这个严格的
separation so first of all design that's
分离，所以首先是
most of us in the room here developers
我们大多数人在这里的房间开发商
are using things like spring and spring
正在使用春天和春天
but-- Gradle and maven to be able to
但是-Gradle和Maven能够
express those dependencies why is the
表达那些依赖性，为什么
developer doing that because the
开发人员这样做是因为
developer best understands the
开发人员最了解
application and understands the
应用程序并了解
dependencies so that one's pretty
依赖，这样一个人很漂亮
straightforward build so first of all
简单的构建，所以首先
the notion here is that you need to
这里的想法是你需要
create a build and you need to create a
创建一个版本，您需要创建一个
deployable artifact that is the artifact
可部署工件，即工件
that runs through the rest of your
贯穿于您的其余部分
application lifecycle so we all know the
应用程序生命周期，所以我们都知道
stories about it works on my machine it
关于它的故事可以在我的机器上运行
doesn't work on my machine and if you
在我的机器上不起作用，如果您
are changing builds then the build
在改变构建然后构建
environment can potentially be the
环境可能是
problem so where is the problem we don't
问题，那么问题不在哪里
know so one of the ways that we can
知道所以我们可以的方法之一
minimize the the different places to
最小化不同的地方
have to look for the problem as we say
正如我们所说，必须寻找问题
we're going to do builds in one place
我们要在一处建造
and then that's going to be the
然后将是
completely automated and repeatable way
完全自动化和可重复的方式
of doing builds that in general is going
做一般的建造
to be your CI system if you don't have a
如果您没有CI，请成为您的CI系统
CI system you absolutely need to get one
您绝对需要获得CI系统
in place there is no way that you can
没有地方，你可以
build software in this new world with
在这个新世界中构建软件
the CI system so what you're going to do
CI系统，所以您要做什么
here at Spring one of course you're
在春季这里，你当然是
going to create a war or a jar file and
要创建战争或jar文件，
the whole point is one build many
重点是很多
deploys and gets away from the anti
部署并远离反
works on my machine a type of response
在我的机器上工作是一种回应
then you're going to create a
然后您将创建一个
lise now who's going to create the
现在，谁来创建
release we believe it is the platform so
发布我们认为这是平台，所以
let me take a moment here the title
让我在这里花点时间
talked about for spring developers we're
谈到春季开发者，我们
going to give you lots of examples of
会给你很多例子
things that are available in spring but
春季可用的东西，
you notice that both of us are on the
您注意到我们俩都在
Cloud Foundry team we believe that a lot
Cloud Foundry团队我们相信很多
of the things that are necessary and
必要的东西
twelve factor are not only satisfied by
十二个因素不仅满足于
the development framework in the
中的开发框架
language but can be best satisfied by
语言，但可以通过以下方式最满意
tooling ie platform I already gave you
工具，我已经给你的平台
the one example a CI system other cloud
一个示例CI系统其他云
platforms can satisfy those other things
平台可以满足其他条件
so for release what we mean is okay
所以对于发布，我们的意思是好的
let's take all of those code bits and
让我们把所有这些代码位和
glue it together with the rest of what
将其与其他东西粘合在一起
we need what's the rest of what we need
我们需要剩下的是什么
well it might be the JDK it might be an
好吧，可能是JDK，可能是
application server it might be the base
应用服务器可能是基础
operating system that you're running on
您正在运行的操作系统
so we need to glue those pieces together
所以我们需要将那些碎片粘合在一起
into something that we call a release
变成我们称为发布的东西
that release is something that we can
该发布是我们可以做到的
then deploy it's something we conversion
然后部署它是我们转换的东西
it's something we can roll back to and
这是我们可以回滚到的东西
so on so this is all about agility and
等等，这一切都与敏捷性有关，
like I said this upgrades and rollbacks
就像我说的那样，升级和回滚
and then finally I want to be able to
最后，我希望能够
take that release and run it and there
获取该版本并运行它
again the platform is all about the
平台再次是关于
platform satisfies taking the release
平台满足发布要求
and running it and there it's all about
并运行它，一切都在这里
speed and you'll see that later on as we
速度，稍后我们会看到
go through some of the demos all right
可以通过一些演示
I'm going to go ahead and skip this
我要去跳过这个
deployment pipeline it'll be in the
部署管道中
slides which will put up on SlideShare
幻灯片将放在SlideShare上
but now let's go back to dependencies
但现在让我们回到依赖关系
for a moment so remember that it's all
一会儿，所以请记住，这就是全部
about repeatable deployments so the the
关于可重复部署，因此
punchline here is that you should never
这里的重点是你永远都不要
assume anything about the environment
对环境承担任何责任
that isn't entirely automated so you
这不是完全自动化的，所以您
need to explicitly declare the
需要明确声明
dependencies but then you can ask the
依赖关系，但是你可以问
question of that runtime eventually
最终那个运行时的问题
there's the runtime environment there's
有运行时环境
the operating system there's the JDK
操作系统中有JDK
there's the application container and so
有应用程序容器，所以
on
上
who's going to specify that is that
谁要指定的是
going to be the developer or the
将成为开发商或
platform and what we're going to do now
平台以及我们现在要做的事情
finally thank you for your patience as
最后感谢您的耐心配合
move out of PowerPoint and take a look
从PowerPoint中移走看看
at some code so I'm going to check my
在一些代码，所以我要检查我的
clock and I'm running super slow so
时钟，我跑得超级慢，所以
let's get going here okay so let's take
让我们去这里好吧，让我们
a look at the code the URL will be on
看看URL所在的代码
the final slide here as well everything
最后的幻灯片以及所有内容
that we're going through here all of the
我们正在经历所有的
samples are available in this github
样本在此github中可用
repository so you can take a look at
仓库，所以你可以看看
that but what we have here is a github
那但是我们这里有一个github
repository that has lots of branches so
有很多分支的存储库
you can see that we've created branches
您可以看到我们已经创建了分支
for all of the different factors and
对于所有不同的因素，
again we're not going to go through them
再次，我们不会经历他们
necessarily all in order we're going to
为了我们要
start here with the f2 f2 dependencies
从f2 f2依赖关系开始
branch now this branch is exactly if you
现在分支该分支正是您
go to this is going to be a spring boot
去这将是一个春天的靴子
app if you go to the spring spring bio
应用程序，如果你去春天spring bio
starter page
起始页
this is the spring boot starter app it's
这是Spring Boot Starter应用程序
exactly that and you'll see if you look
确切地说，你会看看你是否看
inside of the code to take a look at
里面的代码来看看
that now let me come over here and we
现在让我过来
are an f1 code base so again we can see
是f1代码库，所以我们可以再次看到
that you can see all of the branches
可以看到所有分支
here let me get all the screen real
在这里让我得到所有的屏幕真实
estate that I need so I'm going to do a
我需要的房地产，所以我要去做
git checkout oh we're off the bottom of
git checkout哦，我们不在了
the screen so let me scroll that back up
屏幕，让我向上滚动一下
how's that a little more I don't even
我什至什至没有一点
get all the screen real estate
获得所有屏幕房地产
no little more there we go okay
没有更多，我们可以
f2
f2
okay absolutely so I'll scroll it down
好的，所以我将其向下滚动
so you can take a look at it now there
所以你现在可以在那里看看
we go so it's good to have see Davis AFC
我们出发，很高兴见到戴维斯AFC
/ 12 factor app okay and we will give
/ 12因子应用程序还可以，我们会给
you that URLs on the last slide as well
您在最后一张幻灯片上的网址
okay so here we've got f2 dependencies
好的，所以这里有f2依赖项
and I'm going to go ahead and do a build
我将继续进行构建
on this okay so like I said this is just
就这样，就像我说的那样
the standard spring boot app and I'm
标准的春季启动应用程序，我
going to deploy this to the platform so
打算把它部署到平台上
let me do you ACF target and make sure
让我为您设置ACF目标并确保
that I'm in the right place okay there I
我在正确的地方，好吧，我
am I've got my space and so I'm going to
我有我的空间，所以我要
do a CF push and I'm going to point to
做一个CF推，我要指出
the jar file because I built a jar file
jar文件，因为我建立了一个jar文件
and then lo 12 factor now the main thing
然后罗12因素现在是主要的
that I want to show you here so this is
我想在这里告诉你，这是
this is not a talk about cloud foundry
这不是关于云铸造的话题
per se
本身
except that like I said some of these
除了像我说的一些
factors are best realized by a platform
平台最好实现因素
and so what we're doing here is you'll
所以我们在这里要做的是
notice that I just supplied the jar I
请注意，我刚刚提供了广口瓶
did not supply a JDK I did not supply an
没有提供JDK，我没有提供
application container or did I we'll
应用程序容器还是我会
talk about that in just a moment and
谈论一下，
what you see here is you actually see
您在这里看到的是您实际看到的
remember that factor 5 that we went off
记住我们离开的因素5
on and we talked about Design Build
继续，我们讨论了设计构建
release and run what you see right here
释放并运行您在此处看到的内容
on the screen right now as you see
如您所见，现在在屏幕上
what's you see the platform producing a
您如何看待该平台产生了
release remember I said that the release
发布，记得我说发布
is where we take the war file or the jar
是我们存放战争档案或罐子的地方
file and let me scroll up a little bit
文件，让我向上滚动一点
here it releases where we take the code
在这里它释放了我们接受代码的地方
the word the jar file and glue it
单词jar文件并粘贴
together with all of the other stuff
连同其他所有东西
that's needed to just run it so it's
只需要运行它就可以了
glued together with the JDK and the
与JDK和
application container so if we take a
应用程序容器，所以如果我们采用
look here you'll notice that it
看这里，您会注意到
recognized that it was a Java app and it
意识到这是一个Java应用，
grabbed
抓住
the JDK so grab jdk 1.8 and then it went
JDK因此抢到jdk 1.8，然后
ahead and it did the rest of it and now
向前，它做了剩下的一切，现在
you can see that it is in fact running
您可以看到它实际上正在运行
right there greetings from spring boot
就在春季靴的问候
so the app is running now you'll notice
因此该应用程序现在正在运行，您会注意到
that it just pulled in the jdk and that
它只是拉进了jdk，
is because as you know spring boot says
是因为正如您所知， spring boot 说
no we're not going to use excuse me no
不，我们不会使用，请原谅
we're not going to use an external
我们不会使用外部
application server we're actually going
我们实际上要去的应用服务器
to bundle that as a part of the jar
把它捆成罐子的一部分
itself so when we run that jar it has an
本身，所以当我们运行该罐子时，
embedded tomcat inside of it and that's
嵌入其中的tomcat，那就是
what started up now you might say well
现在开始的事情你可能会说得很好
really and in the past if you know
真的，过去，如果你知道
anything about Cloud Foundry in the past
过去有关Cloud Foundry的一切
before spring boot the platform brought
在春季启动之前，平台带来了
the application container
应用程序容器
it brought tomcat so you can ask the
它带来了tomcat，所以你可以问
question of well what's the right way of
那么问题是什么正确的方法
doing things and those that are very
做事情和那些非常
enthusiastic about spring boot will say
对春季靴充满热情的人会说
oh you always bring the application
哦，你总是带上申请表
container as part of spring boot it's
容器是 spring boot 的一部分
always part of the application but I can
始终是应用程序的一部分，但我可以
tell you from working with customers in
告诉您与客户合作
regulated industries that one of the
受管制的行业之一
things that they like is they say you
他们喜欢的事情是他们说你
know what we need to have some control
知道我们需要一些控制
over what that application container is
该应用程序容器是什么
we IT are only going to provide certain
我们IT只会提供某些
application containers so we don't want
应用程序容器，所以我们不想
the developer to make that choice we
开发人员做出选择，我们
want to make that choice now there's a
想做出选择，现在有一个
number of different ways to crack that
多种破解方法
nut but what I'm going to show you here
坚果，但我将在这里向您展示
by switching to a different git
通过切换到不同的git
repository is that I'm going to do a git
仓库是我要做一个git
checkout f2 and I'm going to grab the
结帐f2，我要去抓
other branch so there's another branch
另一个分支，所以有另一个分支
there let me go ahead and do a build on
在那里，让我继续前进，继续前进
that and do a push and I'll show you the
然后推一下，我会告诉你
difference oh if I could type that would
区别哦，如果我可以输入
be great so we'll go ahead and do the
太好了，我们将继续进行
build and then I'm going to push that
建立，然后我要推动
app again there we go and you'll see the
应用程序再次到那里，您会看到
difference in that release process
释放过程的差异
for a moment but the whole point here
片刻，但这里的重点
that you're going to see very very
你会看到非常非常
clearly is that we go through that
显然是我们经历了
release process so again it's just it's
发布过程，所以又是
uploaded or uploading yet uploaded the
已上传或尚未上传
application and now we're going to go
应用程序，现在我们要去
through that process of generating that
通过产生那个的过程
release and here we go you'll notice
放开，我们去了，您会注意到
here that it grabbed the JRE but it also
在这里，它抓住了JRE，但它也
grabbed it did not grab ah I know what
抓了没抓啊我知道了
the issue is
问题是
I pushed the jar not the war exactly
我推罐子不是战争
thank you very much so we'll go ahead
非常感谢您，我们将继续
and kill this so let me show you that so
杀死它，让我告诉你
in the lobstery the first time that we
在第一次的大屠杀中
built we built the jar but when I built
建成我们建成了罐子，但当我建立
the other way and all of this is in
相反，所有这些都在
github you can see the the difference in
github你可以看到其中的区别
the build the Gradle build file so the
构建Gradle构建文件，因此
Gradle build file was the only
Gradle构建文件是唯一的
difference from f2 with the embedded to
从f2与嵌入到
f2 with the external tomcat no changes
f2与外部tomcat无关
in the code
在代码中
none at all it was just a difference in
一点都没有
the build and you'll see that what we do
构建，您会看到我们所做的
instead is we build a war file and so
相反，我们建立了战争文件，所以
instead of pushing the jar file which of
而不是将jar文件推送到
course I got the same thing let's go
当然，我有同样的事情，让我们开始吧
ahead and push the war file and now
向前推动战争档案，现在
you'll see the difference now you'll
您现在将看到差异
notice by the way that there's this 12
顺便说一句，这是12
factor jar dot original and that's
因素罐点原始，那是
because the the Gradle plugin for spring
因为春季的Gradle插件
boot
开机
so there's the Gradle plugin for the jar
所以罐子里有Gradle插件
is sophisticated enough that when it
足够复杂，以至于
came to creating the Gradle plugin for
来为创建Gradle插件
spring boot they didn't want to repeat
他们不想重复的 spring boot
everything that was in the Gradle plugin
Gradle插件中的所有内容
for jar so the way that the spring boot
罐子的方式，这样的春天引导
Gradle plugin works is it uses this
Gradle插件可以用吗
spring boot jar I'm sorry
spring boot 对不起
uses the the jar Gradle plugin takes the
使用jar Gradle插件
output of that which is that original
那是那个原始的输出
that you see and then applies the other
您看到的，然后应用另一个
plug into that jar file so that's why
插入那个jar文件，这就是为什么
you saw the two jar files in the build
您在构建中看到了两个jar文件
directory and so now you can see here
目录，所以现在您可以在这里看到
that in fact it did grab the Junior
实际上它确实抓住了少年
but then it also grabbed Tomcat so you
但是后来它也抓住了Tomcat，所以你
can see here
可以在这里看到
downloading Tomcat it's expanding Tomcat
下载Tomcat，它正在扩展Tomcat
and so on so again the difference is
等等，再次不同的是
really only in the build file okay all
真的只在构建文件中好吗
right so let's go back into our code and
对，所以让我们回到我们的代码中
this right here is a picture of the
这是这里的图片
different layers so when you're
不同的层次，所以当你
deploying an application into the
将应用程序部署到
platform you see that big dotted line
平台上您会看到那条大虚线
remember I said the containers and
记得我说过容器
implementation detail it really is but
实施细节确实是，但是
that is the container and that's all the
那是容器，这就是全部
stuff that's running in the container
容器中正在运行的东西
you've got the host operating system but
您已经拥有主机操作系统，但是
then you've got the OS image that's
然后您得到的操作系统映像是
running inside of the container then
然后在容器内运行
you've got that runtime layer which is
你有那个运行时层
Tomcat the JDK and maybe some other
Tomcat的JDK和也许其他一些
stuff and then you've got the
的东西，然后你有
application at the top and the question
顶部的应用程序和问题
there again is that runtime layer and
再次是运行时层，
you'll see that there are pros and cons
您会发现有优点和缺点
and later on when josh is talking you'll
后来当乔希说话时，你会
see that one of the values of having
看到拥有的价值之一
this layered separation is that it
这种分层的分离是
allows something like a platform team to
允许平台团队之类的人
rev things at the lower layers at the
在较低的层上
blue layers in this diagram and allows
此图中的蓝色层，并允许
the application teams really to stay up
应用团队真的要熬夜
in the application worlds so you don't
在应用程序世界中，所以您不必
have to have things so tightly coupled
必须让事物紧密结合
anymore all right so this is really just
好了，所以这真的只是
the code that's the difference this is
区别的代码是
the embedded runtime and here's the
嵌入式运行时，这是
external runtime you do have to
外部运行时，您必须
explicitly not use the spring boot plug
明确不使用弹簧启动插头
in Gradle plugin because that will
在Gradle插件中，因为这将
always bring in tomcat so you have to
总是带上tomcat，所以你必须
kind of dissect it a little bit and
有点解剖
instead bring in just this plug-in here
而是在这里引入此插件
this dependency management plug-in and
该依赖性管理插件和
specify your dependencies down here so
在这里指定您的依赖关系
all of that is available in the github
所有这些都可以在github中找到
repository all right so two more factors
仓库很好，所以还有两个因素
that I'm going to talk about and then
我要谈论的然后
I'm going to hand it over to Josh so
我要交给乔希
factor number three says configuration
第三因子表示配置
so what you want to do is store the
所以你要做的就是存储
configuration in the environment so
在环境中进行配置
first let's talk about what is
首先让我们谈谈什么是
configuration so configuration is going
配置，以便配置
to be
成为
things like handles to external services
诸如外部服务句柄之类的东西
to databases those types of things
将这些类型的东西数据库化
credentials for example per deploy
凭据（例如，每次部署）
values so maybe some URLs that are
值，因此可能是一些网址
specific to your Prada ploy versus your
特定于您的Prada策略与您的
staging deploy really anything that is
分期部署实际上是
going to differ as you go through the
经历不同的过程
product that the the Application
应用产品
Lifecycle anything that's going to be
生命周期中将要发生的一切
different from dev to tests to prod all
从开发到测试到生产都不同
of that needs to be in a configuration
其中需要在配置中
now we've stored these things
现在我们已经存储了这些东西
historically in a number of different
历史上有很多不同
places we have stored them inside of the
我们将它们存储在
code and I thank my my colleague Matt
代码，感谢我的同事马特
Stein for the Captain Obvious
斯坦因船长
parenthetical remark here yeah you
括号在这里是的，你
should not be hard coding things in your
不应该对您的内容进行硬编码
code but how many people here have code
代码，但这里有多少人有代码
bases where there's probably
在可能存在的地方
configuration hard-coded right we all do
硬编码的配置，我们都可以
it's not just you property files don't
不只是您的属性文件不
put them in property files what wait a
将它们放在属性文件中等待什么
minute isn't that what I'm supposed to
分钟不是我应该做的
do and you'll see an example of that in
这样做，您将在其中看到一个示例
just a bit so the answer is generally
只是一点，所以答案通常是
you're going to be checking things in -
您将要检查的东西-
you're going to be checking the property
您将要检查财产
files into into your source code control
文件放入您的源代码控制
system and so you don't want things like
系统，所以你不想要这样的事情
credentials in there so property files
那里的凭据，所以属性文件
are generally not a good thing the other
通常不是一件好事
thing is that property files are almost
问题是属性文件几乎
always built into the jar or the war
总是内置在罐子或战争中
file and remember I said that one rule
归档，记得我说过一条规则
is that you're not going to do a new
是你不打算做一个新的
build per stage in the lifecycle you're
在您生命周期的每个阶段进行构建
going to do one build many deploys
要做一个建造很多部署
that's another one of the factors that's
那是另一个因素
the next one we talked about and or in
我们谈论的下一个
the application server so where are we
应用服务器，我们在哪里
going to store it well we're going to
要很好地存储它，我们要
store it in the environment so let's
将其存储在环境中，让我们
have a look at that let's jump back over
看一下让我们跳过去
into our code and I'm going to do it
到我们的代码中，我要做
check out another branch environment
查看另一个分支环境
config and what we have in here is that
配置，我们在这里是
same application but now I'm going to
相同的应用程序，但现在我要
parameterize it with an environment
用环境对其进行参数化
variable
变量
so let me go ahead and do a build on
所以让我继续做下去
this and then we'll go ahead and deploy
这个，然后我们将继续进行部署
and while we're deploying I'll take a
在部署过程中，我将采取
look at the code so I'm going to push
看一下代码，所以我要推
and I'm actually going to go back to my
我实际上要回到我的
jar file because I'm going to do
jar文件，因为我要做
everything in the embedded app now so if
现在，嵌入式应用程序中的所有内容都可以
I come over here while we're letting
我在放手的时候过来
that deploy and I'm going to I know that
部署，我要知道
you can't see the URL at the top isn't
您看不到顶部的网址不是
that important anymore so let's come
如此重要，让我们来
over here and go into the environment
在这里进入环境
configuration so what I've done now is I
配置，所以我现在要做的是
have changed it
已经改变了
I've changed my controller is that big
我改变了控制器的大小
enough probably not
可能还不够
is that better okay so the key lines
更好吗，关键是
that we're looking at here is this is
我们在这里看的是
super simple we're going to put things
超级简单，我们要放东西
in the environment variables now how
在环境变量中现在如何
things get into the environment
事物进入环境
variables that's a whole other
完全不同的变量
discussion so how we get things into
讨论，让我们了解如何
those environment variables and in fact
这些环境变量，实际上
you'll see some of that when Josh talks
当乔希说话时，您会看到其中的一些
about some of the other factors in just
关于其他一些因素
a moment but assuming that we've gotten
片刻，但假设我们已经
things in the environment variables what
环境变量中的东西是什么
do I do as an application developer well
作为一名应用程序开发人员，我做得如何？
I'm just going to use something that's
我将要使用的是
available in spring so spring gives me
春天有空所以春天给我
these these libraries that allow me to
这些库让我能够
get into the environment variables very
非常了解环境变量
quickly I implement environment where
我很快实现了环境
you can see here that I'm grabbing those
你可以在这里看到我正在抓那些
environment variables so here's the
环境变量，所以这是
environment variable that I'm interested
我感兴趣的环境变量
in it's a something called who and then
在其中一个叫做谁然后
I change the greeting so in the meantime
我同时更改了问候语
this should have deployed and in fact it
这应该已经部署了，实际上
did so if I curl this again you can see
这样做，如果我再次卷曲，你可以看到
greetings null so the environment
问候为空，因此环境
variable hasn't been set now the
变量尚未设置
environment variable of course is in the
环境变量当然在
container that's up in the cloud so how
云中的容器如何
do I get things up in the cloud well
我能很好地将事情放在云端吗
Cloud Foundry has a nice little command
Cloud Foundry有一个很好的小命令
called set env that allows you to
称为set env，它使您能够
this is a different one we'll get to
这是我们要去的另一种
that in just a moment that allows me to
片刻之后，我就可以
set an environment variable to a value
将环境变量设置为值
and then what I need to do is it says CF
然后我需要说的是CF
restage but I'm actually going to do a
休息，但我实际上要去做
restart and I'll explain that in just a
重新启动，我会在一个
moment that's going to restart the app
即将重启应用的那一刻
now we're restage says I'm going to
现在我们休息说我要去
create a new release in this particular
为此创建一个新版本
case I know that my code is looking up
情况我知道我的代码正在查找
at the looking the environment variables
在看环境变量
up at startup time it's not using those
在启动时就没有使用那些
environment variables at release
发布时的环境变量
generation time if have used those
如果使用了那些
generation time then I would have had to
那时候我就不得不
do a restage but in this case I didn't
休息一下，但在这种情况下，我没有
need to create a new release because
需要创建一个新版本，因为
that environment variable only affected
该环境变量仅受影响
the runtime behavior so now if I go into
运行时行为，所以现在如果我进入
and curl this you can say see it says
并卷曲它，你可以说看到它说
greetings Josh from spring boot so store
来自 spring boot 的乔什问候
the environment store the configure a
环境存储配置
configuration in the environment alright
环境中的配置还可以
one more factor and then we'll hand it
还有一个因素，然后我们会处理
over to Josh for a bit so there's some
到乔希那里，所以有一些
code for picking up at the environment
在环境取货的代码
variables alright so now we're going to
变量很好，所以现在我们要
go we started with factor 1 factor 2 we
我们从因子1因子2开始
went off to factor 5 came back to factor
跳到因子5回到因子
2 now we need 3 now we're going to jump
2现在我们需要3现在我们要跳
all the way head to factor 11 which is
一直到因子11
logs so one of the things of course that
记录日志，这当然是其中之一
you need is you need to be able to read
您需要的是您需要能够阅读
the logs now your applications are
现在您的应用程序的日志
deployed out into the cloud and I need
部署到云中，我需要
to be able to get those log messages so
能够获取这些日志消息，以便
how am I going to do that and the answer
我要怎么做和答案
is that just like environment variables
就像环境变量一样
are kind of a ubiquitous thing that
是一种无处不在的东西
exists in all operating systems that are
存在于所有
accessible by all languages it's kind of
所有语言都可以访问
a de facto standard there's another de
一个事实上的标准，还有另一个
facto standard that is available here on
在这里可用的事实标准
the log side and that is just send
日志端，这只是发送
things to standard out in this standard
在本标准中标准化的事情
error so if you're set sending your log
错误，因此如果您设置发送日志
files to some special log file somewhere
文件到某些地方的特殊日志文件
in some directory then whatever
在某个目录中然后
environment is streaming those law
环境正在流传那些法律
for you is going to have to know about
因为你将不得不了解
that directory or if you're going to
该目录，或者如果您要
stream lot if you're going to write your
流很多，如果你要写你的
log files your log data into some
将您的日志数据记录到一些文件中
database then the system would have to
数据库，那么系统将不得不
know about getting the logs from that
知道从中获取日志
database and so the thing that the
数据库等等
platform can do is if we just say look
平台可以做的就是，如果我们只是说看
just send things to standard out in
只是把东西发送到标准
standard error then the platform says
标准错误，然后平台说
I'll take it from there I'll just go
我从那里拿走我就走
ahead and grab those things so that's
向前拿那些东西，所以
really the thing to do and so let's have
真正要做的事情，所以让我们
a look at that so if we come back over
看一下，所以如果我们回来
here I'm going to do a git checkout f11
在这里，我要进行git checkout f11
and I'm going to go ahead and do my
我要继续做我的
build and we will the build will happen
建立，我们将建立
very quickly and then while it's
很快，然后
deploying we'll go over and take a look
部署，我们将看一看
at the code so there's my push alright
在代码上，所以有我的推动
so let's come over here and take a look
所以让我们过来看看
at the code while that's pushing you go
在代码的推动下，
into my f11 branch there it is into logs
进入我的f11分支，进入日志
the main change in the application here
这里应用程序的主要变化
is that I've of course added all of the
我当然已经添加了所有
standard stuff so if I come down here
标准的东西，所以如果我来这里
into main and into hello you can see in
在主要和你好，你可以看到
the controller that I've added the
我添加的控制器
logger stuff and here you can see that
记录器的东西，在这里您可以看到
I've added the longer stuff and I've
我添加了更长的内容，
added a debug message so log debug and
添加了调试消息，因此记录调试和
there's some other log info stuff over
还有其他一些日志信息
on the application side on the startup
在启动时在应用程序方面
so that's the pretty straightforward
所以这很简单
stuff and that's all fine and good but
东西，一切都很好，但是
we wanted to take it one step further so
我们想更进一步
when you're doing logging you're going
当您进行日志记录时，您将
to have different levels info debug all
具有不同级别的信息调试所有
of that stuff you're going to have those
这些东西，你将拥有那些
different levels so wouldn't it be great
不同的水平，所以不是很好
if I could control those levels without
如果我能控制那些水平而没有
having to do a rebuild somewhere okay
必须在某个地方进行重建
and the answer is you absolutely can so
答案是你绝对可以
if we come down inside of here you'll
如果我们来到这里，你会
notice that we've added a resources
请注意，我们已经添加了资源
directory and in here we have an
目录，在这里我们有一个
application yamo file and that
应用程序yamo文件和那个
application llam
应用程序
eyal identifies and actually defines
正确识别并实际定义
values for those properties that the
这些属性的值
logging packages are looking at so that
正在查看日志记录包，以便
logging package is looking at the
日志记录包正在查看
property logging dot level dot and then
属性记录点级别点，然后
which package so you get to set the
哪个包，以便您设置
logging level for each of the packages
每个软件包的日志记录级别
individually so this is a place where
个别地，所以这是一个地方
you can define those things but wait a
您可以定义这些内容，但请等待
minute didn't I just tell you in the
分钟不只是在
very previous one that you shouldn't
上一个你不应该的
have things that you should configure
有一些你应该配置的东西
things in the environment not in
环境中没有的东西
property files isn't this just a
属性文件不只是一个
property file and the answer is yes
属性文件，答案是肯定的
however this property file the only only
但是，此属性文件是唯一的
only thing that we're using it for is
我们正在使用的唯一东西是
we're using it to be able to have a tree
我们正在使用它来拥有一棵树
structure to my properties so those log
结构到我的属性，以便那些日志
packages are expecting this particular
包期望这个特殊
tree structure for the properties and
属性的树结构和
you'll notice that what this syntax does
您会注意到此语法的作用
right here this syntax is it defines the
就在这里，这种语法定义了
default value of info but it says lookup
信息的默认值，但它表示查找
the actual value from an environment
来自环境的实际价值
variable so I'm right back to
变量，所以我马上回到
environment variables right here okay so
环境变量就可以了
let's go over and have a look this built
让我们过去看看这个内置的
just fine and in fact let me in a new
很好，实际上让我重新
window do a oh and I meant to check this
窗口做一个哦，我想检查一下
this is the big drumroll do we have a
这是大鼓声吗？
proxy in place CF logs see if yep that's
到位CF日志代理，看看是不是
the one CF Apps Co
一家CF Apps Co
okay so this is tailing logs so that's a
好吧，这是拖尾日志，这是一个
good sign so if I now curl this endpoint
好兆头，所以如果我现在卷曲这个端点
greetings Josh and drumroll there we go
乔希和鼓声的问候，我们去了
we're getting some output but one of the
我们得到一些输出，但是其中之一
things you'll notice is first of all I
首先，我会注意到
didn't get the I intend to greet someone
没有得到我打算和某人打招呼
and that's because by default my log
那是因为默认情况下我的日志
level is set to info we'll show you how
级别设置为信息，我们将向您展示
to set that in just a moment but you'll
设置一下，但是你会
notice that I got some log output anyway
注意我还是得到了一些日志输出
and this in fact is log output that the
这实际上是日志输出，
platform is providing it's not
平台提供的不是
application log it's actually something
应用程序日志实际上是
about the context that the applications
关于应用程序的上下文
running in so this shows that a message
在运行，所以这表明一条消息
got routed to my application so let's
被路由到我的应用程序，所以让我们
come back over here and I'm going to do
回来这里，我要去做
that set env again and I'm now going to
再次设置环境，我现在要
set that log level to debug and I'm
设置该日志级别进行调试，我
going to do a CF restart there we go and
要进行CF重新启动，我们去了
that should only take just a moment and
那只需要片刻
then we'll curl it again and by the way
然后我们再顺便卷曲一下
you can see all of the log information
您可以查看所有日志信息
that's coming out here on restart if we
如果我们重新启动会在这里出现
have more time I would go through this
有更多的时间我会经历这个
it's extraordinarily interesting to see
看到这非常有趣
what the platform is doing on your
平台在您身上做什么
behalf as you do a restart in this
代表您在此重新启动
application so you can see here that
应用程序，因此您可以在此处看到
there's some DEA messages there's some
有一些DEA消息有一些
API messages if we look up here and then
API消息（如果我们在此查找）
you can see that there was a whole bunch
你可以看到有一堆
of in fact there's the spring the spring
其实有春天
boot logo should be popping up here
开机徽标应该在这里弹出
somewhere it's a whole bunch of info
某处有很多信息
messages that are coming out Wow a lot
出现的消息很多
okay and now the application started
好，现在应用程序启动了
let's go ahead and curl it and we should
让我们继续并卷曲它，我们应该
see over here in just a moment there we
一会儿在这里看到
go I intend to greet someone so that was
我打算和某人打招呼，所以
the debug message so again you can see
调试消息，以便再次看到
how we controlled that through
我们如何通过控制
environment variables okay so let's come
环境变量好吧，让我们来
back over here and go back into the
回到这里，回到
slides
滑梯
and there is just really the punchline I
我确实有一个重点
like to even though we did live demo I
即使我们做了现场演示
like to have those in the slides for
喜欢把那些放在幻灯片中
your cheat sheets later on and I see
稍后您的备忘单，我看到
somebody taking a photo so let you take
有人拍张照片，让你拍
your photo and then we'll move on okay
您的照片，然后我们继续
so I'm going to hand it over to Josh is
所以我要交给乔希
going to go through a whole bunch more
还要经历一大堆
factors yes question
因素是问题
yeah in fact you'll notice that once or
是的，事实上，您会注意到
the question to repeat the question if
该问题是否重复该问题
you're putting everything to standard
您正在将一切标准化
out in standard error do we have a
在标准错误中，我们有一个
favorite tool that we use to basically
我们常用的最喜欢的工具
parse out of that and the answer is
解析出来，答案是
absolutely so you'll notice that when I
绝对，所以你会注意到，当我
did the CF logs space app name I've
CF记录了我已经使用过的空间应用程序名称
already taken everything impaired it
已经采取一切损害
down to just the app so I've got
只是应用程序，所以我有
platform logs and things like that but
平台日志之类的东西，但是
it was only platform messages that
只是平台消息
pertained to the application
与该应用有关
so there's actually things built into
所以实际上有一些内置的东西
Cloud Foundry that allow you to scope
Cloud Foundry使您可以进行范围调整
your logs to the applications so that's
您的日志到应用程序，所以
number one
第一
then the next thing is well now I've got
那接下来的事情就很好了
a whole bunch of log information in
一堆日志信息
there how do i parse through that we
在那里我如何解析我们
actually use a number of different tools
实际使用许多不同的工具
ourselves when we're operating our
我们在操作自己时
applications in production we use things
生产中的应用我们使用的东西
like we might use like log stash or
就像我们可能会使用日志存储或
Splunk the other thing is that Cloud
Splunk的另一件事是Cloud
Foundry partners with the company that
与公司的代工伙伴
uses an ALK solution that allows you to
使用ALK解决方案，您可以
pipe those logs into an LK Cabana
将这些日志通过管道传送到LK Cabana
environment and then do all sorts of I
环境，然后做各种我
can show you some really really cool
可以给你看一些真的很酷
dashboards that are built in on that as
在其上内置的仪表板
well
好
so the answer is that there's plenty of
所以答案是有很多
stuff built into the Cloud Foundry
Cloud Foundry中内置的内容
platform and then you might also
平台，然后您也可能
integrate with some external log search
与一些外部日志搜索集成
and analytics tools as well ok yes
和分析工具，还可以
another question
另一个问题
it's running multiple instances and your
它正在运行多个实例，而您的
question is what ah so um the logs will
问题是什么啊，那么日志会
basically have enough information in
基本上有足够的信息
there to show you which instances that
在那里向您展示哪些实例
the log message comes from it's a bit of
日志消息来自
a more involved answer but maybe we can
一个更复杂的答案，但也许我们可以
chat a little bit afterward because we
之后聊一点，因为我们
still have a lot of info to cover okay
仍然有很多信息可以解决
all right let me turn off and hand it
好吧，让我关闭并交给它
over to Josh thanks so we've talked a
谢谢乔什，所以我们聊了
lot about 12 factor and how you consume
关于12个因素以及您的消费方式
things from the environment the
来自环境的东西
environment also put some requirements
环境也提出了一些要求
on you and on your application and how
在您和您的应用程序上以及如何
you build it right 12 factors a set of
您建立正确的12个因素集
axioms one of the most important ones
公理是最重要的公理之一
that seems really generic on the surface
表面上看起来真的很普通
and in terms of requirement it is you
就需求而言，就是你
have to start fast the reason you have
必须快速启动您拥有的原因
to start fast is you can't do this list
快速启动是您无法执行此列表
of things if you don't deploy scale
如果不部署规模的话
release and recover the the cloud is
发布和恢复云是
going to kill you at most days right
最多会杀死你几天
hardware dies in AWS data centers will
AWS数据中心中的硬件模具将
shift VMs out from underneath you in
将VM从您下方移入
Cloud Foundry right all kinds of stuff
Cloud Foundry对各种东西的权利
happens so if your app can't start
发生，所以如果您的应用程序无法启动
quickly you're not able to recover from
很快您就无法从中恢复
kind of just what is a normal day-to-day
只是正常的日常情况
operation you also have to shut down
操作还必须关闭
gracefully when you're given a signal
收到信号后优雅地
right sector' normally you have to do
正确的部门通常需要
this basically so you can start right if
这基本上是这样，如果
we if we look at kind of typical
如果我们看典型的
problems I've had in my career where my
我在职业生涯中遇到的问题
apps didn't shut down gracefully I end
应用没有正常关闭我结束
up with things like lock jobs and
处理锁定作业和
databases I end up with like late
我最终发现的数据库很晚
database connections hanging and then my
数据库连接挂起，然后我的
SAS database services like oh you have
SAS数据库服务之类的哦
50 connections you can't have another
50个您无法再拥有的连接
one you also start to lose track of
你也开始失去对
where you are so you have to take this
你在哪里所以你必须采取这个
to kind of stuff into account when you
当你考虑到某种东西
build and design your apps so that's
构建和设计您的应用，以便
kind of something to remember right
需要记住的东西
you'll see that the app we had though
您会看到我们拥有的应用
it's basic starts up fairly quickly even
它的基本启动甚至很快
large spring boot apps tend to start up
大型Spring Boot应用倾向于启动
very fast and as long as you're not
很快，只要你不在
loading a bunch of data from a database
从数据库加载一堆数据
say before you expose a rest interface
在公开休息界面之前先说
you're fine the other thing to remember
你还可以记住另一件事
about this right is 12 factor was
关于这个权利是12个因素是
written by a platform provider just like
由平台提供商撰写，就像
Cloud Foundry Heroku GAE
Cloud Foundry Heroku GAE
Bua pass we have to make intelligent
Bua通行证，我们必须变得聪明
decisions about your application and we
关于您的应用程序的决定，我们
can only do that in terms of starting
只能从开始做起
with the concept of a timeout right so
有超时的概念，所以
if your app doesn't come up in some
如果您的应用程序没有出现
amount of time we've got to call it dead
我们必须称其为死时间
so starting quickly is very important to
所以快速开始对
have success in these environments
在这些环境中取得成功
I think factor four is really the most
我认为第四要素确实是最重要的
important factor it's it basically says
重要的是它基本上说
that you have to access us everything
您必须访问我们的所有内容
through the environment right Cornelia
穿过环境Cornelia
has showed us an example of this already
已经给我们展示了一个例子
where we greeted me through an
我们通过一个
environment variable but this gets more
环境变量，但这会得到更多
complicated as we start to look at our
当我们开始看看我们的
applications and they're kind of the
应用程序，它们是
real topologies right we have databases
我们拥有数据库的真实拓扑
we have message queues and we have those
我们有消息队列，我们​​有那些
databases and message queues in very
数据库和消息队列非常
different environments so we have to
不同的环境，所以我们必须
have a way to take this one artifact
有办法拿走这件神器
point in two different databases and
指向两个不同的数据库，
different message queues every time we
每次我们有不同的消息队列
deploy it and the way we do that is we
部署它，而我们这样做的方式是
access the environment through a locator
通过定位器访问环境
so Cloud Foundry has an environment
所以Cloud Foundry有一个环境
variable called vcap services that we
我们称为vcap服务的变量
use to encode all of this information
用于对所有这些信息进行编码
other systems will use different things
其他系统将使用不同的东西
I know
我知道
Heroku for example gives you a bunch of
以Heroku为例，
environment variables per connection or
每个连接的环境变量或
per backing service the reason we do
每个后勤服务我们这样做的原因
this right is so we can change the
这项权利是这样，我们可以更改
locations of those things there's kind
这些东西的位置
of a three-step process here that we'll
我们将分三步走
walk through and then we'll look at the
穿过，然后我们看一下
code to consume it the first thing you
将其消耗掉的代码
have to do is create the thing that you
要做的就是创造你的东西
need to talk to you right so this is the
需要和你说话，所以这是
Cloud Foundry command to spin up a new
Cloud Foundry命令启动新的
my sequel instance for our example app
我的示例应用程序的续集实例
that's where we're going to store our
那就是我们要存储我们的地方
information this is a Cloud Foundry
信息，这是一个Cloud Foundry
command which will connect your my
命令将连接您的我的
sequel instance to your application and
应用程序的后续实例
the net result of this is you now have
最终的结果是您现在拥有
an environment variable inside of your
您内部的环境变量
container in your particular deploy that
您特定部署中的容器
tells you where your database is so
告诉您数据库在哪里
you're going to have a JDBC connection
您将拥有一个JDBC连接
string inserted you're going to have
您将插入的字符串
environment just using a username and
仅使用用户名和
password that last command is kind of a
最后一个命令的密码
drag right there's a lot of ceremony and
向右拖动有很多仪式，
if I have to run all these commands
如果我必须运行所有这些命令
every time I deploy my application one
每次我部署我的应用程序
of two things happens we forget to do
有两件事发生了，我们忘记做
things and then we have unexpected
事情，然后我们有意外
results or our CI systems get really
结果或我们的CI系统得到了真正的
really complicated Cloud Foundry has
真正复杂的Cloud Foundry具有
something called a manifest that lets us
被称为清单的东西可以让我们
declare what our application should be
声明我们的应用程序应该是什么
should look like and how it should be
应该看起来像，应该怎样
deployed so we're going to use that
部署，所以我们将使用它
we're going to
我们要
look at the different it's a second and
看看不同的是一秒钟，
we'll see that we've kind of changed the
我们会看到我们已经改变了
way we deploy and so the commands will
我们部署的方式，因此命令将
have changed a little bit the most
变化最大
important thing to get your head around
重要的事情要打转
at the very bottom is that services
最底层是服务
thing where we declare that we're going
我们声明要去的东西
to depend on a service name pelo DB if
依赖于服务名称pelo DB，如果
that service doesn't exist if we don't
如果我们不提供该服务就不存在
see that environment variable our
看到我们的环境变量
application will fail to deploy and this
应用程序将无法部署，这
is good right because now our deploys
是很好的权利，因为现在我们的部署
will fail fast because backing services
将很快失败，因为支持服务
are missing so I'll go back over here
不见了，所以我会回到这里
and we'll look at backing sorry about
我们会看看支持抱歉
that
那
backing services
支持服务
so the first thing to note right is the
所以首先要注意的是
manifest we just saw this in the slide
清单，我们刚刚在幻灯片中看到了
this is the same thing inside of our
这是我们内部的同一件事
Gradle built or build file we've made a
Gradle构建或构建文件，我们制作了一个
couple of new declarations if you've
如果您有几个新的声明
been to the spring cloud in particularly
特别是去过春云
a spring cloud talk where they've talked
他们谈论过的春天的云谈话
about the connectors this should look
关于应该看起来的连接器
familiar
熟悉的
we're including a dependency on the
我们包括对
service connection library and then
服务连接库，然后
we're including a specific dependency on
我们包括了对
the service connection library for Cloud
Cloud的服务连接库
Foundry right I said earlier that
我刚才说过的铸造厂
platforms will expose these variables in
平台将在
different ways or these config in trees
不同的方式或这些在树中的配置
in different ways this is the one that
以不同的方式，这就是
understands how Cloud Foundry does it
了解Cloud Foundry是如何做到的
we've included two other libraries and
我们包括了另外两个库
I'll go over them in their opposite
我会在他们对面越过它们
order we've said the runtime must have a
我们已经说过的顺序，运行时必须有一个
my sequel driver in it and we've also
我的续集驱动程序，我们也
declared a dependency on flyweight so
声明了对flyweight的依赖，因此
we're going to push an application which
我们将推送一个应用程序
needs a database schema we're going to
需要我们要使用的数据库架构
just let flyweight create that for us
只要让举重为我们创造
now and we'll come back to why we let it
现在，我们将回到为什么我们让它
do that in different ways we can
以不同的方式做到这一点
manipulate it when we talk about the
当我们谈论
12-pack the other thing to orient
12包装其他东西定向
yourself is we've made some structural
你自己就是我们做了一些结构上的
changes to our service
我们服务的变化
our controller now has a service
我们的控制器现在有服务
injected it's Auto wired right and then
注入它的自动接线，然后
we've added we've changed kind of the
我们添加了我们已经更改了
route we've made it possible to pass a
路线，我们通过了
person to greet as a request parameter
作为请求参数打招呼的人
everything else is pretty much the same
其他一切都差不多
we call our service which does a save we
我们称我们的服务可以节省我们
get the time that we greeted somebody
得到我们打招呼的时间
and we make a date out of it and we save
我们用它做个约会，然后保存
the name this is backed by a spring crud
这个名字是由春天结团支持的
repository that comes out of spring data
来自Spring数据的存储库
what does it data JPA the really easy
它对JPA的数据有何作用？
interface project which you can see in
您可以在其中看到的界面项目
right there right so this all looks
就在那里，所以这一切看起来
pretty normal pretty pretty vanilla
很普通很漂亮香草
spring out this seems like it would work
跳出这似乎会起作用
just about anywhere so we'll go and
几乎在任何地方，所以我们去
we'll check out this app
我们将检查这个应用程序
we live on the edge and see if we need
我们生活在边缘，看看是否需要
those commands sweet so we'll go ahead
这些命令很贴心，所以我们继续
and build this I'm going to do the blue
并建立这个，我要去做蓝色
green to it so Cornelia makes a good
绿色，让Cornelia很好
point if we look at the apps we have now
如果我们看看我们现在拥有的应用程序
we have our original app and it's still
我们有我们原始的应用程序，它仍然
up and running it's not connected to
启动并运行它没有连接到
anything but it is known by a URL right
除了URL知道的任何东西
hello 1212 f dot c FF spied at IO for
你好1212 f dot c FF在IO处窥探到
the rest of the presentation will deem
演示文稿的其余部分将视为
this our production URL and we'll push
这是我们的生产网址，我们将推送
our apps will mess around with them to
我们的应用程序将与他们混乱
verify that they work and then we'll cut
验证它们是否有效，然后我们将削减
over prod so right this is how people
过度生产，所以这是人们的方式
will come to know our apps from from the
将会从中了解我们的应用
outside world so the the command has
外界，所以命令有
changed a little bit I'm going to just
改变了一点，我将要
for safety's sake make sure we clean up
为了安全起见，请确保我们进行清理
our environment because I'm paranoid
我们的环境，因为我很偏执
so this command I've just run says trash
所以我刚刚运行的这个命令说垃圾
my database set our environment back to
我的数据库将环境设置为
normal I think we already did this but I
正常，我认为我们已经做到了，但是我
just had like kind of a scary thought
只是有种可怕的想法
and I don't want a demo to fail so I've
我不希望演示失败，所以我已经
asked Cloud Foundry to spin us up anew
让Cloud Foundry重新振兴我们
my sequel instance that we can then
我的续集实例
later bind to this will give us an empty
以后绑定到这个将给我们一个空
database and at this point when it's all
数据库，到此为止
done we'll push the app up so you can
完成后，我们将向上推送该应用程序，以便您可以
see a couple of things have changed in
看到几件事发生了变化
our output right we're pushing the same
我们的输出权，我们正在推动相同
app but the name has changed so we'll
应用程序，但名称已更改，因此我们将
have two instances of the two different
有两个不同的两个实例
versions of our app running essentially
本质上运行的应用程序版本
it's created a random route for us
为我们创造了一条随机路线
because I didn't want to have to fuss
因为我不想大惊小怪
with not matching and not finding a URL
与不匹配并且找不到URL
so it just generated a bunch of random
所以它只是产生了一堆随机
words after the name of our app for us
对我们而言，我们的应用程序名称后面的单词
it's going to try to bring it up and fly
它会尝试使其飞起来
away if you're unfamiliar with it just
如果你不熟悉它就走了
kind of by default if you don't do
默认情况下，如果您不这样做
anything in a spring boot app you
春季启动应用中的任何内容
declare the dependency and you just
声明依赖关系，而你只是
don't write any more code kind of like
不要再写类似的代码了
most things just works and it has a
大多数事情都可以，并且它有一个
default behavior so we have a database
默认行为，所以我们有一个数据库
migration that'll create a schema for us
迁移将为我们创建一个架构
it's a pretty basic table that maps to
这是一个非常基本的表，可以映射到
our class we can see it in here so we
我们的班级，我们可以在这里看到它，所以我们
just create a table with three columns
只需创建一个包含三列的表
an ID that's auto-generated a date that
自动生成日期的ID
says when I was ever was greeted and
说我什么时候受到欢迎
then the first name of the person we're
然后是我们这个人的名字
greeting this is specific and we want to
问候这是具体的，我们想
call that out because that's important
喊出来，因为那很重要
you'll see that in when we talk about
当我们谈论时，您会看到
environments and how they should be the
环境以及它们应该如何
same this is only going to work on my
同样这只会在我身上起作用
sequel right that that schema create
该模式创建的续集权
isn't going to work on another platform
不会在另一个平台上工作
that's different than how we've done
这与我们的工作方式不同
things for a long time right but twelve
事情很久了，但是十二点
factors very opinionated that we should
因素非常认为，我们应该
always work with the version and the
始终使用版本和
type of service we intend to work with I
我们打算与我合作的服务类型
could have to make my life easier when I
我可能不得不让我的生活更轻松
was developing this originally run h2
正在开发此最初运行的h2
locally but then I would have had to
在本地，但那时我不得不
duplicate all this work there's
复制所有这些工作
obviously other solutions to this and
显然还有其他解决方案
I'm a pretty big fan of pragmatism do
我是实用主义的忠实粉丝
what works for you but if we're going to
什么对您有效，但是如果我们要
follow the spirit of 12 factor this is
遵循12要素的精神是
the guidance right we only interact with
我们只与之互动的指导权
my sequel because that was our intention
我的续集，因为那是我们的意图
so now our app is up and running and we
所以现在我们的应用程序已启动并正在运行，我们
can curl it again
可以再次卷曲
but we're going to have to use this new
但是我们将不得不使用这个新的
URL sorry I operate Cloud Foundry more
URL很抱歉，我更多地使用Cloud Foundry
than I curl apps so we curled it and we
比我卷曲的应用程序，所以我们卷曲它，我们
see that we've added a default right we
看到我们已经添加了默认权限，我们
saw that the default value of people to
看到人们的默认值
greet was nobody we can get a little
没人欢迎，我们可以得到一点
more whoops formal
更多的正式
we can greet Cornelia we've also added a
我们可以问候Cornelia我们还添加了一个
history API that'll just give us
历史API只会给我们
so we can see that we've created a
这样我们可以看到我们已经创建了一个
couple of people and we get some nice
几个人，我们得到一些好
round numbers there which we'll talk
四舍五入的数字，我们将谈论
about a little bit as far as when we did
大约和我们做的时候差不多
that so we've greeted two people at this
所以我们在这问候了两个人
point and our app is up and it's running
点，我们的应用程序启动并且正在运行
and we've decided it's good so let's go
我们已经决定这很好，让我们开始吧
ahead and do this the rest of this
继续做，其余的
Bluegreen deployment where we make it so
我们做到的蓝绿色部署
this app will respond to production
这个应用程式会回应生产
traffic as well so if we run CF routes
流量也是如此，如果我们运行CF路由
we can say CF map - route
我们可以说CF地图-路线
I'll get the usage because I don't
我会用的，因为我没有
remember the command
记住命令
we will tell the name of our app and the
我们将告诉我们应用的名称以及
domain that we want to add and then
我们要添加的域，然后
we'll tell it the host name so now
我们现在告诉它主机名
something interesting should happen when
什么时候应该发生一些有趣的事情
I start to curl this application
我开始卷曲这个应用程序
we said before our default with nobody
我们说过我们默认之前没有人
so we should see when we do this the
所以我们应该在执行此操作时看到
requests will bounce between both apps
请求将在两个应用之间反弹
so the Cloud Foundry route or routes
因此Cloud Foundry路线
randomly we can see in the output there
我们可以在输出中随机看到
sometimes it greeted me sometimes it
有时它打招呼我有时
greeted nobody right so everybody
向所有人打招呼，所以大家
believe me now that we're bouncing
现在相信我，我们正在反弹
traffic between both instances of our
两个实例之间的流量
app we would go ahead at this point and
应用程序，我们将在这一点上继续前进，
decide to cut overwrite our new version
决定削减覆盖我们的新版本
is good and the old one is bad but we've
是好的，旧的是坏的，但是我们已经
done a zero down time to put one of the
零停机时间将其中一个
interesting things is we've actually
有趣的是我们实际上
made a really big functionality change
进行了重大的功能更改
to how our app works without our user
在没有用户的情况下我们的应用程序如何工作
ever seen downtime yes there may have
有没有见过停机时间，可能有
been some things we had to manage on the
这是我们必须管理的一些事情
back end but our customer didn't see it
后端，但我们的客户没有看到
so we can say CF unmapped route actually
所以我们可以说CF未映射路线
we can just be a little more aggressive
我们可以变得更具侵略性
CF stop
CF停止
hello 12 F so we can see that the old
你好12 F，所以我们可以看到旧的
version is stopped now and if we curl we
版本已停止，如果我们卷曲，我们
just see that nobody records we also
只是看到没有人记录我们
note that our history API is still
请注意，我们的历史记录API仍然
worked we're getting back JSON so that's
工作我们返回了JSON，所以
the takeaway right we've added a
外卖权，我们添加了一个
database we deployed the app and we
数据库，我们部署了应用程序，然后
didn't really do anything in the code
并没有在代码中做任何事情
other than say spring cloud spring cloud
除了说春天云春天云
cloud foundry and my sequel connection
Cloud Foundry和我的续集联系
spring cloud went through our
春天的云穿过我们
environment interrogated what was shown
环境审问了所显示的
to us if we look at the environment for
如果我们考虑环境
the container we can see that it
我们可以看到它的容器
injected a bunch of stuff that wasn't
注入了一堆不是的东西
there before about our database
关于我们的数据库之前
including the host name and the JDBC URL
包括主机名和JDBC URL
and all that other stuff
还有其他所有东西
where's the play button that works
播放按钮在哪里起作用
so this is the takeaway from this
所以这是外卖
section and this factor is really
部分，这个因素确实
important because it's foundational to
重要，因为它是基础
making everything else work our code has
使我们的代码具有其他功能
to build with the knowledge of something
用某物的知识建造
right our code built in this instance
正确在此实例中构建的代码
with a lot of help from spring so we
在春季的帮助下，所以我们
didn't have the down-and-dirty of what
没有什么的卑鄙
the environment variable was called had
环境变量被称为
we looked at Python or had we looked at
我们看过Python还是看过
Ruby or something that had a little bit
Ruby或有些东西
less Cloud Foundry magic behind it we
少了Cloud Foundry背后的魔力
would have seen very explicit
本来会很明确
I need a variable called vcap services
我需要一个名为vcap services的变量
in this case spring cloud took us care
在这种情况下，春云照顾我们
that for us when we staged our app we
对于我们来说，当我们上演我们的应用程序时，
built that stuff into the release so we
在发布中内置了这些内容，因此我们
knew that there had to be a thing called
知道必须有一个叫做
hello DB in the container and when we
您好在容器中的DB以及当我们
built that it's called the droplet the
建立它称为液滴
thing we deploy we shoved all that stuff
我们部署的东西推了所有这些东西
in there so all that information was
在那里所有的信息都是
available to us from that point forward
从那时起对我们可用
when we went to run the app the app
当我们去运行该应用程序时
started and it looked for a thing and it
开始，它寻找一个东西，它
found a thing by the name of hello DB
用hello DB的名字找到了一个东西
and it pulled out the credentials and it
然后拿出凭证
was able to communicate with it
能够与之交流
so that's that's really the whole point
所以这就是重点
of factor for is you have to talk to
原因是您必须与
backing services by consuming them from
通过从中使用服务来支持服务
the environment if you do it another way
环境，如果您以其他方式这样做
you're not able to move around right I
你不能四处走动
could take this application and I could
可以接受这个申请，我可以
deploy it into our another space or
部署到我们的另一个空间或
production environment so if I say see
生产环境，所以如果我说看
if target sure what's called cofactor
如果目标确定什么叫做辅因子
we can see in the space I have no apps I
我们可以在空间中看到我没有应用
do have a service so I'm going to push
确实有服务，所以我要推动
our app again so I haven't changed
我们的应用程序再次，所以我没有改变
anything
任何东西
I'm not rebuilding anything I'm going to
我不会重建任何我要去的东西
spell pusher hit and we'll watch the app
按下拼写推动器，我们将观看该应用程序
go up and we'll see a new random URL
上升，我们将看到一个新的随机URL
that gets generated it is generated for
被生成的是为
us so our app is a different instance
我们，所以我们的应用程序是一个不同的实例
that will respond on a different
会以不同的方式回应
location and I'll talk to different data
位置，我将讨论不同的数据
so in a minute when this comes up we'll
所以一分钟后，我们会
be able to see that the database is
能够看到数据库是
empty but the reason we do this write it
空的，但我们这样做的原因是将其写入
so we can deploy to multiple places for
这样我们就可以部署到多个地方
different reasons to make life easier
使生活更轻松的不同原因
we'll talk about what that enables in
我们将讨论在
just a second here when this comes up
出现时请稍等一下
and I prove you guys that it works
我向你们证明它有效
actually let's start to talk about that
实际上让我们开始谈论这个
while this goes on so the next factor is
虽然这样下去，所以下一个因素是
dev prod parody right you can see where
开发人员模仿模仿权，你可以看到
I'm going with this production and
我要去生产
staging it should be the same similar is
分期应该是一样的相似是
great the same is better we've all in
太好了，我们都参加了
our career spent a lot of time screwing
我们的职业生涯花了很多时间
around with o the prod box doesn't look
产品目录框周围没有出现
like mine on prod box or well I develop
像我的产品盒上的，还是我开发的
on a Mac and I spent things up inside of
在Mac上，我把东西花在里面
Eclipse and then I wonder why it doesn't
Eclipse，然后我想知道为什么它没有
work when I ship it off to wherever my
当我将其运送到任何地方时都可以工作
code goes AWS whatever right these are
不管这些是什么，代码都会转到AWS
problems that it's undifferentiated
没有区别的问题
heavy lifting right we just waste a lot
繁重的举动吧，我们浪费了很多
of time doing stuff that shouldn't
时间做一些不该做的事情
happen this is way more important when
发生这种情况在以下情况下更重要
we start to talk about cloud native apps
我们开始谈论云原生应用
because they're designed for continued
因为它们是专为持续
to be continuously deployable so if we
可以持续部署，所以如果我们
got to go through all that ceremony of
必须经历所有的仪式
verifying that like I checked it in and
像我签入一样验证
it worked on my local box and it worked
它可以在我的本地盒子上工作
in the staging environments a little bit
在分阶段环境中
different and how are we ever going to
不同，我们将如何去
know it works in prod right this parody
知道它可以在这个模仿产品中发挥作用
becomes really really important it lets
变得非常重要，它让
us go fast so we have in the environment
我们走得快，所以我们在环境中
that we're working on today we have
今天我们正在努力
effectively a CI environment and we have
有效的CI环境，我们拥有
a product usually there's another step
产品通常还有另外一步
called acceptance with the workflow we
在工作流程中我们称为接受
use it pivotal labs where somebody will
在关键实验室使用它
come and they'll bless a particular
来，他们会祝福一个特殊的
commit but by whatever you process you
承诺，但无论您处理了什么
follow you'll make commits to your
跟随你将对你的承诺
source code and you'll make changes and
源代码，您将进行更改，
eventually you'll decide or as a team or
最终，您将决定还是作为一个团队或
however you do it that we have one we
但是你这样做，我们有一个我们
want to look at and this content is
想看看，这个内容是
exactly what we need and we should be
正是我们需要的，我们应该
ready to go
准备好出发
mr. product owner or product manager do
先生。产品负责人或产品经理
you want to deploy they'll make the call
您想部署他们会打电话
and they'll say yes this is how it works
他们会说是的，这是如何运作的
for us so we deploy version 201 and now
为我们服务，所以我们部署201版及现在
that app is live but we didn't do
该应用程序已上线，但我们没有
anything additional to it right we just
除了它，我们还有其他任何东西
ran CF push and it was out and it's gone
运行CF推送，它消失了，它消失了
the reason that works is because there's
起作用的原因是因为
parody with all these environments they
他们模仿所有这些环境
all have their own values for
都有自己的价值观
environment variables but they all use
环境变量，但它们都使用
the same environment variables this lets
相同的环境变量
us go fast and it's repeatable so we can
我们走得快，它是可重复的，所以我们可以
do it over and over again and every
一遍又一遍地做
commit becomes a candidate for a
提交成为候选人
deployment so our operators should they
部署，因此我们的运营商应该
have and it should an ease arise can
拥有并且应该容易出现可以
come back this is a really good need
回来，这是一个非常好的需求
right they can come back they can patch
他们可以回来，他们可以修补
the platform and they can redeploy
平台，他们可以重新部署
software so there's a lot of power that
软件，所以有很多功能
we get by leaning on the platform and
我们靠在平台上
relying on the platform to be the same
依靠平台是一样的
that makes sense to everybody
这对每个人都有意义
any questions so as we go back here our
任何问题，以便我们回到这里
app is up and running and we can do a CF
应用已启动并正在运行，我们可以进行CF
curl
卷曲
and we'll see that greets nobody and if
我们会看到这招呼没人，如果
we look at the history we only have one
我们看看历史，我们只有一个
entry
条目
so right use a platform it's the same
所以正确使用平台是一样的
because it's the same it takes all the
因为都是一样的
guess in a way did that factor 12 is my
猜想那个因素12是我的吗
least favorite factor 12 factor was
最不喜欢的因素12的因素是
written with an opinion and a bias
有观点和偏见
towards apps that ran with repple
对使用repple运行的应用程序
shelves so when you look at admin tasks
货架，所以当您查看管理任务时
this becomes very very obvious where
这变得非常非常明显
somebody's like hey I can spit up a
有人像嘿，我可以吐了
shell and I can SSH into this thing and
shell，我可以通过SSH进入
I can kind of do whatever I want because
我可以做任何我想做的事，因为
I've got this really great freeform kind
我有这种非常棒的自由形式
of plug-in way to interact with my
与我互动的插件方式
environment we don't have that in Java
Java中没有的环境
right that's just not a thing for us so
对，那对我们来说不是什么，所以
we have to treat this factor a little
我们必须稍微对待这个因素
differently the spirit of the law says
法律的精神不同
admin processes run against a release we
管理流程针对我们发布的版本
can totally do that our tools are geared
完全可以做到我们的工具适应了
to do that it should run in an identical
为此，它应该以相同的方式运行
environment that's totally fine
完全可以的环境
it should use the same code base and
它应该使用相同的代码库
same config I think that makes a lot of
我认为相同的配置
sense it's weird because it looks like
感觉很奇怪，因为它看起来像
something we've been telling people not
我们一直在告诉人们
to do for a long time but in kind of
做很长一段时间，但有点
advanced cases you end up with these
先进的案例，你最终与这些
multi projects Gradle files which feels
多项目Gradle文件的感觉
a little wrong every time I do it I'm
每次我做错我
liking that's not right
喜欢那是不对的
your admin code should absolutely live
您的管理员代码应该绝对有效
with the coded administrates on that's
与编码的管理员
why we end up in these multi project
为什么我们最终参与这些多项目
situations the thing I want to call out
情况下我想呼唤的东西
is this has a lot of rules be pragmatic
这有很多规则是务实的吗
right do what works that's the most
正确地做最有效的事情
important thing I got wrapped around the
我被包裹的重要
axle by this this last week right we had
上个星期我们有了这个车轴
a lot of talks about the 12th factor and
关于第十二因素的很多讨论和
how much it was pissing me off to do the
有多少让我生气的事
right thing
正确的事
so the point where like I stayed up till
所以直到我熬夜
2:00 in the morning before this trying
尝试之前的凌晨2:00
to make it work and I was finally like
使它工作，我终于喜欢
forget it oops too far so we're going to
忘了它太远了，所以我们要
grab a new version of our app and that
抓取我们应用的新版本，然后
app is going to have a small change I
应用程序将有一个小变化我
talked earlier about this date didn't
早先谈到这个日期没有
have much fidelity I'm going to go back
有很多保真我要回去
to the other space so we can use our
到另一个空间，以便我们可以使用我们的
nice URL
不错的网址
so we'll build that and then we'll kick
因此，我们将其构建，然后开始
off the deploy and we'll look at what's
下部署，我们将看看
different
不同
sorry
抱歉
so if we orient ourselves again there's
因此，如果我们再次定位自己，
nothing different in our build file we
我们的构建文件没有什么不同
still depend on the same stuff right
仍然依赖相同的东西
flyways still there we've we've done one
仍然有飞路，我们已经完成了一项
kind of new thing we've decided that the
我们已经决定，
fidelity we were getting out of the time
保真度过我们时间
we greeted somebody was not very good
我们向某人打招呼不是很好
the way we set up the database
我们建立数据库的方式
originally it was a think column in all
最初它是所有的思想专栏
stores a date so when we did our history
存储日期，以便我们进行历史记录时
API you saw we got the same number every
您看到的API每个都有相同的编号
time it's because it was midnight
时间是因为是午夜
midnight today we the product manager
今天午夜我们是产品经理
said they would like better so we've
说他们想要更好，所以我们已经
gone and we've made a small change which
走了，我们做了一个小小的改变
i think is probably easiest to see if we
我认为可能最容易看出我们是否
just dip it against the last branch for
只需将其浸在最后一个分支上
so before we had a date now we're using
所以在我们约会之前，我们正在使用
the UNIX epoch seconds and then we can
UNIX纪元秒，然后我们可以
see the way that change is trickled down
看到改变的方法
to our through our code where we've got
通过我们拥有的代码
you started using along instead of a
您开始沿用而不是
date right all the way down through our
一直到我们的约会
all the way down to our entity class
一直到我们的实体类
we've also had to create a new database
我们还必须创建一个新数据库
grace migration for this
为此进行宽限期迁移
I picked a weird example intentionally I
我故意挑了一个奇怪的例子
wanted something that my sequel would
想要一些我的续集会
choke on if we did the right thing so
如果我们做对了就窒息
right we create a new table we give it a
对，我们创建一个新表，我们给它一个
temp name we insert or we change the
我们插入的临时名称或我们更改的
layout of that table so initially it
该表的布局，因此最初是
will match the exact same columns is the
将匹配完全相同的列是
greeting table so we alter it to just
问候表，所以我们将其更改为
take a big int instead of a date we grab
取一个大整数而不是我们抓住的日期
everything and we do a transform so it
一切，我们进行了改造，所以它
matches the format we expect in the new
与我们期望的新格式匹配
table and then we copy the old one to a
表，然后我们将旧表复制到
backup because we probably don't want to
备份，因为我们可能不想
lose the old stuff in case something
丢掉旧东西以防万一
goes rogue in this process and then we
在这个过程中流氓，然后我们
copy the temp table over to a new table
将临时表复制到新表
so this is awesome right my app can do
所以这是我的应用可以做到的很棒的权利
this what sucks is I have to take down
这很烂，我必须记下来
time because it's a database migration
时间，因为这是数据库迁移
and it's a real one so earlier
这是一个真正的早期
Cornelia's version of the app and my
Cornelia的应用程式版本和我的
version of the app could run because we
该应用程序的版本可以运行，因为我们
didn't share a dependency now if I was
如果我当时不共享依赖
to push to a new application we would
推送到一个新的应用程序，我们将
share a dependency and we would have a
分享一个依赖，我们会有一个
problem right there would be some sort
问题吧，那会有某种
of conflict how it manifests itself who
冲突如何体现自己
knows I think what really happens is we
知道我认为真正发生的事情是我们
would end up corrupting the database and
最终会损坏数据库，并且
then none of them would work right in
然后他们都不会在
the real world that's actually that's
真实的世界是
absolutely what happens right for our
绝对适合我们的情况
trivial app we might get away with it if
琐碎的应用程序，如果
there was no request coming in so what
没有请求进来怎么办
we're going to do in the simple case is
在简单的情况下，我们要做的是
just have flyweight run the migration
只是让flyweight运行迁移
for us right the the way flyweight works
对我们来说，举重的工作方式是正确的
is it looks for files with certain
它是否在寻找具有特定含义的文件
naming convention so on the class path
在类路径上的命名约定
it looks in DB migration if it sees
它会在数据库迁移中查看
something called v1 it runs that and
叫做v1的东西可以运行
then it sees something called v2 and it
然后它看到一个叫做v2的东西
runs that and it just so on and so forth
运行它，依此类推等等
and order so it's going to run during
和订单，因此它将在运行期间
the push for us during application
申请过程中对我们的推动
startup it's going to migrate the table
启动它将要迁移表
for us so we'll see that our app is up
为我们服务，因此我们将看到我们的应用已启动
and running now
现在运行
and if you know the demo gods are
如果你知道示范神
smiling we'll see what we had in there
微笑着，我们将看到里面的东西
before
之前
big thing the necklace here right we ran
一件大事，我们跑来的项链
curl against the thing a whole bunch of
卷曲整个东西
times earlier the times are all the same
时间早了，时间都一样
so if we were to add a new person if we
所以如果我们要添加一个新的人，如果我们
were to greet somebody new my boss left
问候我老板离开的新人
the back of the room so we'll use his
房间的后面，所以我们用他的
name
名称
we can now see that we've got a time
现在我们看到有一段时间
with a little bit more fidelity right so
保真度更高一点，所以
that happened all on the fly we ran our
这一切都是在飞行中发生的，我们跑了
admin process it happened in the
管理过程发生在
container it happened against the same
容器发生在相同的位置
config obviously because we've
配置显然是因为我们已经
manipulated our database and everything
操纵我们的数据库以及所有内容
was good when you can do this I would
当你可以做到的时候我很好
say do it right that was really easy I
说对了，那真的很容易
can take downtime life is good we could
可以度过一生的美好生活
have gotten super crazy about how we
对我们如何变得超级疯狂
manage the database and done the
管理数据库并完成
migration on a snapshot and brought that
迁移快照并带来了
back and reconcile the differences so
返回并调和差异，以便
there are ways to solve kind of zero
有办法解决零
downtime problems with database
数据库宕机问题
migrations and admin processes they're
迁移和管理流程
just a lot of work so you know rule
只是很多工作，所以你知道规则
number one about factor 12 if you can
如果可以的话，因子12排名第一
take downtime take downtime moving
停工停工
forward though things get more
前进，尽管事情会变得更多
complicated and sometimes you do just
复杂，有时你只是
want a separate app in the github repo
在github仓库中想要一个单独的应用程序
and because we're running short on time
而且因为我们时间紧迫
I'm not going to cover it there's an
我不会掩饰它的存在
example for how we would do this and
我们如何做到这一点的例子
basically we just move all the flyweight
基本上，我们只是移动所有的轻重物
stuff into another app and build it as a
填充到另一个应用程序中并将其构建为
multi project build so that is the end
多项目构建，到此为止
of my section and we're back to Cornelia
我的部分，我们回到Cornelia
for a report binding all right so we
一份有约束力的报告，所以我们
just have a couple more to go through
还要再经历几个
here one of the first things is that
这是第一件事
we're going to talk about is factor
我们要谈论的是因素
seven so again you can see we're going
七点，你又可以看到我们要去
out of out of order here and really the
乱序在这里，真的
punchline about poor findings is that
关于不良发现的一句口号是
let the platform handle that for you
让平台为您处理
so one of the challenges as you're
所以你面临的挑战之一
moving things through the application
通过应用程序移动事物
lifecycle or if things are changing even
生命周期，或者即使情况正在发生变化
in your Prada environment is if you're
在您的Prada环境中，如果您是
having to change ports and you're having
不得不改变端口，而你不得不
to go in and change some configuration
进入并更改一些配置
somewhere and oh my gosh I now this is
某个地方，哦，天哪，我现在这是
running somewhere else and I have a
在其他地方跑，我有一个
different URL or I have a different port
不同的URL或我有不同的端口
you have to handle all that port stuff
你必须处理所有这些端口的东西
yourself and so really the whole point
你自己，所以整个重点
here is that allowed allow something
这是允许允许的东西
like the platform to handle that for you
就像平台为您处理
and in the cloud native application
并在云原生应用程序中
platforms remember that was that the
平台记得那是
quote at the very beginning are designed
一开始的报价是设计好的
to do exactly that so let's go ahead and
要做到这一点，让我们继续前进，
take a look at that
看看那个
let's see okay you're at that URL great
让我们看看你在那个URL上很棒
I just want to make sure so let's do get
我只想确保让我们开始
check out on factor seven port bindings
查看因子7端口绑定
I'm going to do a build and then we're
我要进行构建，然后我们
going to go ahead and deploy it and then
继续进行部署，然后
I'm going to jump over to a picture
我要跳到一张照片
while we're waiting on the deploy CF
在我们等待部署CF时
push okay there goes the deploy so let's
推好，那里有部署，所以让我们
go back here and take a look at a
回到这里，看看
picture then so here's what happens in
图片，那么这就是发生的情况
Cloud Foundry so what I have is I have a
Cloud Foundry所以我拥有的是
number of different machines out there
那里不同机器的数量
that we're calling runners those runners
我们称跑步者为跑步者
are I talked about it as an
我是否把它说成是
implementation detail but the
实施细节，但
implementation detail is here that
实施细节在这里
they're creating containers and my apps
他们正在创建容器和我的应用
are running in containers so in this
在容器中运行，所以在此
picture here you see two different
在这里看到两个不同的图片
runners which are two different virtual
两个不同的虚拟跑步者
machines they're each broken down into
他们每个都被分解成的机器
different containers and you can see
不同的容器，你可以看到
that those are running and the way that
这些正在运行以及
port mappings happen is this when we go
我们去的时候端口映射就是这样
to hello 12 factor it goes into a
打招呼12个因素
routing component that's part of the
路由组件是
platform that routing component has
路由组件具有的平台
essentially a table that maps to and it
本质上是一个映射到它的表
says oh I see that hello 12 factor is
说哦，我看到你好12要素是
mapped to this application instance
映射到此应用程序实例
that's over here and it's mapped down to
在那边，它被映射到
a URL like 192 168 227 and a port okay
像192168227这样的URL和端口就可以了
and that port is written and I'll show
该端口已写入，我将显示
you what what the difference we're going
你，我们要做什么区别
to see this in the code in just a moment
一会儿就能在代码中看到
and it handles that port you'll notice
它会处理您会注意到的端口
that I never configured I never said
我从未配置过，我从未说过
port 61 Oh 21 I never gave it a port but
端口61哦21我从未给它端口
that's all handled for you and we'll get
一切都为您处理，我们会得到
back to this picture in just a moment I
回到我的那张照片
can have multiple instances and in fact
可以有多个实例，实际上
I'll point it out right now you'll
我马上指出，你会
notice here that I've got two different
注意这里我有两个不同
runners they have two different URLs 192
跑步者有两个不同的URL 192
1 68 227 and dot 33 but the ports are
1 68 227和点33，但端口是
locally scoped so I might in fact have
本地范围，所以我实际上可能有
the same port number running on two
在两个端口上运行相同的端口号
totally different machines now imagine
现在完全不同的机器
if you had to manage ports across an
如果您必须管理跨
entire district distributed environment
整个地区的分布式环境
of different virtual machines that would
不同的虚拟机
complicate the matter even further so
使事情变得更加复杂
don't go there get a platform that does
不要去那里得到一个平台，可以
this for you so let's come back here
这个给你，让我们回到这里
great things deployed just fine so I'm
很好的东西部署很好，所以我
going to go ahead and I'm going to curl
继续前进，我要卷曲
this and you'll see that what we've done
这样，您会看到我们已经完成了
in this application is we have I don't
在这个应用程序中，我们没有
want the history I just want this what
想要历史，我只想要这个
did I do oh there we go the 12 I was
我做了吗，哦，我们去了12我
going to say are the demagogues not
要说的是煽动者不是
smiling on me okay so now you can see
对我微笑好吧，现在你可以看到
here that it's greeting nobody and
在这里，它没有问候任何人，
here's the IP address of the machine
这是机器的IP地址
that is running that application and I
正在运行该应用程序，而我
can curl this again and you can say see
可以再次卷曲，你可以说看到
here's the port numbers and it turns out
这是端口号，事实证明
that there is a facility here in in
在这里有一个设施
Cloud Foundry that allows you to
Cloud Foundry使您能够
actually have set the port internally
实际上是在内部设置端口
and then it maps to an external port so
然后它映射到外部端口
you do have the best of both worlds that
您确实拥有两全其美的优势
you can do some of that configuration
你可以做一些配置
yourself and we'll take care of the port
您自己，我们会照顾港口
bindings for you so that mapping so I
为您绑定，以便映射，所以我
can keep curling this and keep curling
可以保持卷曲并保持卷曲
this and I'm always going to get back
这个，我总是要回去
that same IP address and the same port
相同的IP地址和相同的端口
now let's get back to the next factor
现在让我们回到下一个因素
and the next factor is about stateless
下一个因素是无状态
processes so when you're deploying your
因此，当您部署自己的
app applications up there in the cloud
云中的应用程序应用程序
here's what your cloud looks like in the
这就是您的云在
beginning you might be running on one
开始你可能会跑一个
one machine and then you things are
一台机器，然后你就是
going better and you need more load and
变得更好，您需要更多的负载，
you add additional machines and then all
您添加其他计算机，然后全部
of a sudden your app goes viral and you
突然间，您的应用程式开始流行，而您
need to scale out to tons of instances
需要扩展到大量实例
so you've deployed now 10
所以你现在已经部署了10
and instances of your application
和您的应用程序实例
because your hello world is so freaking
因为你好，世界好可怕
cool that everybody's looking at it
很酷，每个人都在看它
right well if you look in an environment
如果您在环境中看就很好
like this where I've got hundreds or
像这样我有数百个或
thousands or tens of thousands or maybe
成千上万
hundreds of thousands of machines
数十万台机器
something's breaking all the time
一直在破坏
there's always something going down and
总是有东西掉下来，
I can tell you that when you're google
我可以告诉你，当你在谷歌
searching there's machines going down
搜索有机器故障
all the time but it still keeps working
所有的时间，但仍然可以正常工作
I can keep going back and I can get my
我可以继续往前走，我可以得到我的
search results and I can go from page
搜索结果，我可以从页面转到
one to page two and you know what a
一到二页，你知道什么
machine may have died the machine that I
机器可能已经死了，我的机器
was just getting my response from may
只是得到我可能的回应
have died in the process and so the
在此过程中死亡，因此
whole point here and this factor six is
整个要点，这个因素六是
all about designing for failure that's
关于为失败而设计
the why of it and so what this what the
为什么呢，那又怎样呢？
statelessness does is if you stick with
无国籍是如果你坚持
stateless apps it allows the platform to
无状态应用程序，它允许平台
do all sorts of things for you so let's
为您做各种事情，所以让我们
take a look at that so I'm going to I
看看那个，我要去
probably should have put this I could
大概应该把这个我可以
have saved myself a little bit of time
节省了自己一点时间
but we're going to do a check out a the
但是我们要去检查一下
next factor and we're going to do a
下一个因素，我们将要做一个
Gradle build and then we're going to
建立Gradle，然后我们将
deploy this see yeah push alright and so
部署这个，看，推，好吧，等等
what we're doing now is I'm redeploying
我们现在正在做的是重新部署
that app you'll see that the change that
该应用程序，您将看到
I made in it actually I just added
我所做的实际上是我刚刚添加的
another endpoint so I'm going to
另一个端点，所以我要
simulate one of those explosions in one
模拟其中一种爆炸
of the machines so I'm going to simulate
的机器，所以我要模拟
my application dying and I want to show
我的应用程序快要死了，我想证明
you something it relates back to the
你与它有关的东西
port bindings and I'm looking at the
端口绑定，我在看
clock I realize I only have about two
时钟我意识到我只有两个
minutes to go which is we're going to
分钟，这是我们要去的
make it we're going to make it stick
做到这一点，我们要坚持下去
with me so for the deploy all this takes
和我一起进行部署
just a couple of minutes but once this
只是几分钟，但是一旦
comes up you'll see in just a moment
一出现，您很快就会看到
that I've simulated as I said I've
我已经说过我已经模拟过
simulated this application dying and
模拟了此应用程序即将消亡并
there's something very very interesting
有一些非常有趣的事情
about that because it comes back to the
关于这一点，因为它回到了
point about port bindings so the port
关于端口绑定的问题，所以端口
bindings you remember I said things are
你记得我说的东西是
changing maybe the
改变也许
courts are changing and we're going to
法院正在改变，我们将
see an example of that in just a moment
马上看到一个例子
and if those things are changing all the
如果这些事情改变了所有
time you don't want to manage it
不想管理的时间
yourself today to live in this cloud
今天就自己生活在这朵云中
native world you absolutely have to
您绝对必须的本地世界
automate everything so you cannot manage
自动化一切，所以您无法管理
your applications and your deployments
您的应用程序和部署
and your upgrades all by yourself
您自己升级
anymore
不再
you need to have some help and that's
您需要一些帮助，那就是
where a platform comes in ok so if we
平台可以进入哪里，所以如果我们
now curl this you can see here that my
现在卷曲这个，你可以在这里看到我的
app is up and running I'm now running on
应用已启动并正在运行我现在正在运行
10.10 81 16 port 6368 5 so I can keep
10.10 81 16端口6368 5所以我可以保持
doing this and now in this particular
这样做，现在特别
case though I'm going to access a new
虽然我要访问一个新的
URL that I have in my app which is this
我的应用程式中有这个网址
broken URL and you'll see that I got
URL损坏，您会看到我
back some Jason that I wasn't expecting
回到我没想到的杰森
ok I'm hitting both CF apps your version
好的，我同时打了两个CF应用程序
of the app is hello spring 1 see if
该应用的名称是hello spring 1，请查看是否
delete that's right
删除是正确的
we're load balancing over that delete
我们正在对该删除进行负载平衡
sorry hello spring 1 that's what I
抱歉，你好，春天1，我就是这样
thought was going to hit you earlier but
以为会早点打到你，但
then you did the blue green instead ok
那你做了蓝绿色反而还好
so let's do the curl again and there we
所以让我们再做一次卷翘
go it says up some things something's
它说了一些事情
broken now if we do CF apps we can see
如果我们使用CF应用程序，现在会坏掉
that at the moment only one in zero
目前只有零分之一
instances of that one application I want
我想要的那个应用程序的实例
one running but the one is not running
一台正在运行，但一台没有运行
anymore so if I do a CF apps and I'm
再这样，如果我做一个CF应用程序，
wondering whether the demo gods are not
想知道演示神是否不是
going to smile on me
要对我微笑
it says requested state is stopped CF
它说请求的状态已停止CF
restart
重新开始
hello 12 factor did I kill the wrong one
你好12因素我杀错了吗
this should only take just a moment the
这只需要片刻
requested state was stopped so what I
请求状态已停止，所以我
needed was the requested state starting
需要的是请求的状态开始
which is why it's not there and I know
这就是为什么它不存在的原因，我知道
I'm over I promise I'm finishing up here
我结束了，我保证我会在这里结束
I just killed it okay
我刚刚杀了好
so no it's I'm deployed to the wrong
所以不，是我被错误地部署了
application so I'm just going to go
应用程序，所以我就去
ahead and close out that's how you know
前进并结束这就是你所知道的
it's real is that the demos don't always
真实的是演示并不总是
work happy to show this to you on a
很高兴在手机上向您展示
break immediately following so the final
紧接着休息，所以最后
factor that I want to talk about here is
我想在这里谈的因素是
concurrency so we're all familiar with
并发，所以我们都熟悉
the scale-up model so if you need more
放大模型，因此如果您需要更多
and more capacity you just give it more
和更多的能力，你只是给它更多
memory or you give it more CPU power and
内存，或者您赋予它更多的CPU能力，
so on in the cloud native world you
在云原生世界中
scale out use you build your
扩展使用，您可以建立自己的
applications in such a way that if I
应用程序，如果我
need if my hello world app goes viral
如果我的hello world应用程序具有病毒性，则需要
and I need more instances I just deploy
我需要部署更多实例
more instances it's very very simple
更多实例非常非常简单
that's the way it works so what we have
这就是它的工作方式，所以我们拥有
here is we've got a bunch of different
这是我们有很多不同的地方
workloads and by the way those workloads
工作量以及这些工作量
aren't just web apps they might be
不只是网络应用
background processes it might be
可能是后台进程
different process types and when you
不同的过程类型以及何时
scale out you're just going to scale out
扩大规模，就扩大规模
additional instances now here I was
现在我在这里还有其他实例
going to show you a scale demo and I was
要给你看一个规模演示，我当时
going to show you how quickly and one of
会告诉你如何快速，其中之一
the punch lines is I was going to scale
最重要的是我要按比例缩放
from one app instance to five app
从一个应用程序实例到五个应用程序
instances and it literally happens that
实例，它确实发生了
additional app instances start up in
其他应用程序实例在以下位置启动
about a second and remember all the way
大约一秒钟，并一直记住
back to factor five where we split out
回到分解的第五因子
design build release and run and we said
设计版本发布并运行，我们说
release bundles everything up so that
发布将所有内容捆绑在一起，以便
run can happen very quickly that's what
运行会很快发生，这就是
the platform does for you so that
该平台为您服务，以便
release process allows you to scale to
发布过程使您可以扩展到
additional instances and I won't have
其他实例，我将没有
the time to show you that demo last
是时候向您展示该演示了
couple of things that's not all we have
几件事不是我们所拥有的
some additional bonus factors we do want
一些我们想要的额外奖金因素
you to think about auditability of your
您考虑一下您的可审核性
applications and it's not just your
应用程序，而不仅仅是您的
responsibility in fact that's another
责任其实是另一回事
thing that as the developer you can
作为开发人员，您可以
push on to the platform so having the
推到平台上，使
platform provide auditability what's
平台提供可审核性
running where when did it start
在哪里开始运行
all of those event streams and so on and
所有这些事件流等等
that's already part of the Cloud Foundry
那已经是Cloud Foundry的一部分
platform the other thing that you need
平台您需要的其他东西
to think about is you need to think
想想是你需要思考
about writing applications in such a way
关于以这种方式编写应用程序
that you can external from the
你可以从外部
application apply off authorization and
申请取消授权并
authentication against those so role
对那些角色进行身份验证
based access control against URLs that's
基于URL的访问控制
the important thing is against URLs and
重要的是反对URL和
in fact a couple of these come from our
实际上，其中一些来自我们
colleague Josh McEntee we were just
同事Josh McEntee我们只是
having this debate in the last week so
在上周进行了辩论，因此
thank you very much we'll leave you with
非常感谢你，我们会留给你
just a couple of things we can recommend
我们可以推荐的几件事
a couple of upcoming sessions so there's
几个即将举行的会议，所以有
a spring boot for DevOps so a lot of
DevOps的 spring boot ，所以很多
what we've been talking about here is
我们在这里谈论的是
DevOps ish so spring boot for DevOps
DevOps应运而生，因此春季启动DevOps
there's a presentation happening
有一个演讲正在发生
immediately after the break at 10:30 the
在10:30休息后立即
other one that Josh was talking a lot
另一个乔什在说话的人
about spring cloud there's a spring
关于春天的云，有一个春天
cloud services talk this afternoon at
云服务今天下午在
two-30 that Scott and Craig are doing I
斯科特和克雷格正在做的两个30
strongly encourage you to go take a look
强烈鼓励您去看看
at that it's going to give you a really
这样会给你一个真正的
good idea about how some of these
关于其中一些的好主意
factors are implemented in the spring
因素在春季实施
context and I already mentioned the
上下文，我已经提到了
migrating the monolith and there again
迁移整体并在那里再次
is the URL of the repository that has
是具有以下内容的存储库的URL
all of the examples that we just showed
我们刚刚展示的所有示例
you and and will stick around for a
你，并会坚持一个
little bit if you have any questions so
如果您有任何问题的话
thank you very much for your attention
非常感谢您的关注